with we believed
私たちは信じていました
President Zhang, distinguished guests, welcome to today's feast of knowledge
張会長、ご来賓の皆様、今日の知識の饗宴へようこそ
So today we are very honored to invite President Zhang Guoen, President of National Normal University
本日は、国立師範大学の張国恩学長をお迎えできることを大変光栄に思います。
Demonstration universities are leaders in domestic education circles
実証大学は国内教育界のリーダーである
So today he will talk about a topic that also belongs to his profession.
そこで今日、彼は自分の職業にも属するトピックについて話します。
Research on the Application of Information Technology in Education
教育における情報技術の活用に関する研究
Principal Zhang is a very outstanding scholar in this field
張校長はこの分野で非常に優れた学者です
He was once a professor and librarian at the National Model University
彼はかつて国立モデル大学の教授兼図書館員でした。
Professor and Vice-Chancellor and then President of Model University since February 2010
2010 年 2 月よりモデル大学の教授、副学長を経て学長を務める
He's very young. He's 47 years old.
彼はとても若いですね、47歳です。
So I think he is the youngest national university president in the country
つまり彼は国内最年少の国立大学学長だと思います
But he just reminded me that there is another one, but the scale of the school cannot be compared with the Normal University.
ただ、もう一つあるのですが、その学校の規模は師範大学とは比べものにならないと彼は思い出させてくれました。
So he's a very young, promising and highly academically accomplished principal.
つまり、彼は非常に若く、将来有望で、学業においても非常に優れた校長です。
He is a very representative scholar in his field
彼はその分野において非常に代表的な学者です
He has won two National Science Council Excellence Awards
彼は全米学術会議優秀賞を2回受賞しています。
a total of six years
合計6年間
he too
彼もです
Executive Director of Zhizhihui
知志会常務取締役
especially important
特に重要な
As far as I know, he is the founder of the Digital Learning Quality Certification Center
私の知る限り、彼はデジタル学習品質認証センターの創設者です
centralized builder
集中ビルダー
Then this center is in my impression
それから私の印象ではこのセンターは
Certification and Promotion of Digital Learning in Taiwan
台湾におけるデジタル学習の認証と推進
had a great effect
大きな効果がありました
Professor Zhang and I have a special marriage
張教授と私は特別な結婚生活を送っています
Because of a national action plan funded by the National Science Council
米国科学会議が資金提供する国家行動計画のため
Digital Archives and Digital Learning National Program
デジタルアーカイブとデジタル学習国家プログラム
Then this year and next year will end
それで今年も来年も終わる
So this project is ten years old
つまりこのプロジェクトは10年目になります
what about this plan
この計画はどうですか
It turned out to be two plans
2つのプランになりました
One is the national travel plan for digital point leaders
1つはデジタルポイントリーダー向けの全国旅行プランです。
One is the National Roadmap for Digital Learning
1 つはデジタル学習のための国家ロードマップです。
National Travel Plan for Digital Point Leaders
デジタルポイントリーダーのための全国旅行計画
In my impression
私の印象では
at the very beginning
一番最初に
Should be the first in the world
世界初のはず
with the power of the country
国の力で
The Power of a National Action Plan
国家行動計画の力
to drive digit length
桁の長さを駆動する
then digital learning was established later
その後デジタル学習が確立されました
Probably the first in the world
おそらく世界初
I'm not sure about this part
この部分についてはよくわかりません
Directly the first of its kind to promote digital learning with a national program
国家プログラムでデジタル学習を直接促進するこの種のものとしては初めて
The two programs were later merged
2 つのプログラムは後に統合されました
then it's a very special project
それならそれはとても特別なプロジェクトです
More than ten years ago, the logarithmic point was long
10年以上前は対数点が長かった
Including me can be said to have no idea
私も含めて何も知らないと言える
I don't know what is the digit length
桁の長さがわかりません
After ten years I think many people
10年経てば多くの人がそう思う
At least you've heard the term
少なくともあなたはこの用語を聞いたことがあるでしょう
even know how
方法さえ知っています
and it's easy to do
そしてそれは簡単です
Nobody heard of digital learning even a decade ago
10年前ですらデジタル学習なんて誰も聞いていませんでした
At least I'm not familiar with this myself
少なくとも私自身はよく知りません
But now Taiwan's top 1,000 companies
しかし今では台湾のトップ1,000企業に
Basically almost all have been more or less
基本的にほぼすべてが多かれ少なかれ
Using digital learning to train employees
デジタル学習を使用した従業員のトレーニング
So I think the development of these two fields
したがって、これら 2 つの分野の発展は、
It's very special in our country
私たちの国ではとても特別なことです
Principal Zhang Guoen is a leader in digital learning
張国園校長はデジタル学習のリーダーです
He just said what I just introduced
彼は私が今紹介したことを言っただけです
Digital Learning Quality Certification Center
デジタル学習品質認証センター
He is the founder and general convener
彼は創設者であり総招集者です
And he also serves as a digital point chief
彼はデジタル ポイント チーフも務めています
Co-host with Digital Learning National Initiative
Digital Learning National Initiative との共催
I am the host
私がホストです
So the co-hosts of the digit-long segment
したがって、桁長のセグメントの共同主催者は
Center Adult Principal
中心大人校長
He used to be the director of the Information Institute, Zhongyan Information Institute
彼は以前、中燕情報研究所の所長を務めていました。
He is the person in charge of the digital learning side.
デジタル学習側の責任者です。
So today we are very honored
ですから今日はとても光栄です
Can invite such an important scholar
こんなに重要な学者を招待できるのか
Let's talk about a subject he's doing well
彼が得意なテーマについて話しましょう
Research on the Application of Information Technology in Education
教育における情報技術の活用に関する研究
We welcome Mr. Zheng with warm applause
鄭氏を温かい拍手でお迎えします
Thanks
ありがとう
We thank Mr. Wang Huyan
王滬燕氏に感謝します
In addition, there are many old seniors of mine here.
また、ここには私の古い先輩もたくさんいます。
and our school teachers
そして私たちの学校の先生たち
and classmates
そしてクラスメート
In addition, representatives from various
また、様々な国の代表者が、
then i want to be very happy
それなら私はとても幸せになりたいです
And it's a great honor to be here
そして、ここに来られることはとても光栄です
Share our information technology with you
私たちの情報技術をあなたと共有しましょう
Applications and research in education as part of
教育における応用と研究の一環として
Then I think this field has developed to the present
その後この分野は現在に至っていると思います
In fact, it's been almost 20 years
実に20年近く経ちますが、
from the earliest very simple
最初から非常にシンプルな
One is used in the classroom
1台は教室で使用しています
We call it the Association for Integrating Education
私たちはそれを「教育統合協会」と呼んでいます。
Until now, apart from the integration of information into blood
これまで、血液への情報の統合とは別に、
but also promote to industrial application
産業への応用も促進する
Especially the computer has changed a lot
特にコンピュータは大きく変わりました
Now there are camp technology and mobile technology
今ではキャンプテクノロジーとモバイルテクノロジーがあります
So its platform is getting more and more complex
そのため、プラットフォームはますます複雑になっています
then we all know the theory of trading
そうすれば、誰もがトレーディングの理論を知っています
It's a hundred years old It's a hundred years old
それは百年です、それは百年です
But this century-old history usually takes place in
しかし、この百年にわたる歴史は通常、
Classroom Inside the actual classroom
教室 実際の教室内
a result obtained
得られた結果
But now there is an information platform
しかし今は情報プラットフォームがある
The information platform is very complicated
情報プラットフォームは非常に複雑です
A platform with a marketing platform A platform with mobile technology
マーケティングプラットフォームを備えたプラットフォーム モバイルテクノロジーを備えたプラットフォーム
Internet-based platform
インターネットベースのプラットフォーム
Of course there are platforms for personalized learning
もちろん、パーソナライズされた学習のためのプラットフォームもあります
So under such a platform
したがって、そのようなプラットフォームの下では
we may have to rethink
私たちは再考する必要があるかもしれない
Think about how to develop
どう開発するかを考える
A Variation in Trading Theory
トレーディング理論のバリエーション
how to apply
適用する方法
Put information technology on top of our entire school
学校全体に情報技術を導入します
There are also students' self-learning
学生の自習もあります
But because of such Yangu
でもそんな楊貴妃のせいで
It does raise a lot of questions
多くの疑問が生じます
what's the problem
どうしたの
Children often forget themselves as long as they are in front of the computer
子どもたちはコンピューターの前にいる限り、自分自身を忘れてしまうことがよくあります。
so there will be a phenomenon of fame
それで名声現象が起こるだろう
The so-called poisoning happened.
いわゆる中毒事件が起きた。
It's very easy to develop a warm habit
温かい習慣を身につけるのはとても簡単です
If Xin Xin gets used to it, there will be a big problem
Xin Xinがそれに慣れてしまったら、大きな問題が発生するでしょう
big problem
大問題
So he does have a lot of hangovers
だから彼は二日酔いが多いんだ
that under such aftermath
そのような余波の下で
how do we apply it
それをどのように適用するか
At present, Taiwan is integrating information into classroom teaching.
現在、台湾では教室での教育に情報が組み込まれています。
I think there should be a history of 15 years
15年くらいの歴史はあるはず
Now most of the teachers have the means to use computers to help his teaching
現在、ほとんどの教師は、授業を支援するためにコンピュータを使用する手段を持っています。
The student also has the means to use the computer to aid his own learning
学生は自分の学習を助けるためにコンピュータを使用する手段も持っています
So where is the problem now?
それで、今、問題はどこにあるのでしょうか？
Today's technology changes too much
今のテクノロジーは変わりすぎます
Because there are many sequelae
後遺症が多いから
So how do we import more bone-setting places
では、より多くの接骨場所をインポートするにはどうすればよいでしょうか
Then let this bone-setting place make a greater contribution to education
そして、この整骨院が教育にさらに貢献できるようにしましょう。
I will go to the mainland for a while
しばらく本土に行きます
Central China Normal University
華中師範大学
That's when I knew they had a big, big plan.
その時、彼らが大きな大きな計画を持っていることを知りました。
Taiwan probably can't compare
台湾は比べられないかもしれない
It is also a plan to promote information and agriculture into teaching
情報と農業を教育に活用する計画でもある
Related to Elanin
エラニン関連
His promotion is an astronomical figure
彼の昇進は天文学的な数字だ
300 billion RMB
3,000億元
is very scary
とても怖いです
Therefore, it means that the production value of this supernatural power is also very large.
したがって、この神通力の生産額も非常に大きいということになります。
but we also know
しかし、私たちも知っています
They hardly know how to push
彼らは押し方をほとんど知りません
He's a lot like what we were like twenty years ago
彼は20年前の我々によく似ている
When information first arrives in education
情報が教育に初めて導入されるとき
don't know how to push
押し方がわからない
So from an industry point of view
したがって、業界の観点から見ると、
Our business opportunity is great
私たちのビジネスチャンスは大きい
we can make their money
私たちは彼らのお金を稼ぐことができます
but we can teach him what was ten years ago
しかし、私たちは彼に10年前のことを教えることができます
After he had reached ten years ago
彼が10年前に到達した後
We have progressed for ten years
私たちは10年間進歩してきました
So use an angle like this
そこでこのような角度を使ってみましょう
In addition to this, there is actually another very important
これに加えて、実はもう一つ非常に重要なことがあります
There may be a big change recently
最近大きな変化があるかも知れません
Twelve Years International
十二年インターナショナル
In fact, in the past 12 years, I think about Taiwan's future development
実はこの12年間、私は台湾の将来の発展について考えてきました。
If we look at it from a long-term perspective
長期的な視点で見れば
It can indeed change the entire education pattern
それは確かに教育パターン全体を変える可能性があります
at least three years
少なくとも3年
It used to be six years, now it's three years more
以前は6年でしたが、今はさらに3年です
Therefore, there are nine years in which normal news can be obtained.
したがって、正常なニュースが得られる期間は9年となります。
We know that it should be under the joint examination system
合同審査制度のもとで行うべきであることは承知しております。
So our students' academic achievement
それで、私たちの生徒の学力は
Academic achievement of our students High academic achievement
学生の学業成績 高い学業成績
It does not mean that its future competitiveness is high
将来的な競争力が高いわけではない
Especially in the era of Internet, computerization and technology
特にインターネット、コンピュータ化、テクノロジーの時代では
you have so much ability we must develop
あなたには私たちが開発しなければならないたくさんの能力があります
For example, we often say that we want to promote night reading
たとえば、私たちは夜の読書を促進したいとよく言います。
children need to read more night
子どもたちは夜にもっと本を読む必要がある
But the ranking of our night reading
でも夜の読書ランキングは
Ranking is not high in the world
世界的に見てもランキングは高くない
I'm not tall, I remember like
私は背が高くない、覚えているのは
is better than that one
あれよりも良いです
One that is lower in Macau
マカオではもっと低い
Macau is a gambling country
マカオはギャンブルの国です
We come in for night reading part is lower than theirs
私たちは夜の読書に来ましたが、パートは彼らよりも低いです
How could such a problem be caused?
このような問題はどのようにして引き起こされるのでしょうか?
Because our education stage
なぜなら私たちの教育段階では
from primary school
小学校から
First grade through high school
小学1年生から高校まで
We never teach students to find jobs
私たちは学生に仕事を見つけるように教えることは決してありません
We also never teach students
私たちは生徒にも決して教えません
Get it from reading
読んで得する
get very interesting
とても面白くなる
we just let him read
私たちはただ彼に読ませるだけです
But you can see
しかし、あなたは見ることができます
when do we teach young children
幼い子供たちにいつ教えますか
Organize knowledge from professional reading
専門的な読書から知識を整理する
Find out the key points in the professional reading
プロの読書で重要なポイントを見つける
These organize knowledge and find out the key points
知識を整理し、重要なポイントを見つけ出す
It is often made by our Pingliang
弊社の平涼社でよく作られています。
we are not now
私たちは今ではありません
Middle school has to take the entrance exam for high school and high school has to take the exam for university
中学校は高校受験、高校は大学受験が必要です
There are many booksellers who have created many Pingliang editions.
平涼版を数多く出版している書店はたくさんあります。
how to organize this
これをどのように整理するか
Then I said why this sequelae
それから私はなぜこの後遺症が残るのかを言いました
getting bigger
大きくなって
There are too many things to read in the Internet age
インターネット時代には読むべきものが多すぎる
is on the Internet
インターネット上にあります
But even this basic quality
しかし、この基本的な品質さえも
did not build
構築しませんでした
Information provided by the Internet age
インターネット時代の情報提供
Instead, many students
その代わりに多くの生徒が
students are a burden
学生は負担だ
is a burden
負担です
So there is a side effect like too many
したがって、多すぎるような副作用があります
So I said why the influence of the country will be so great in 12 years
それで私はなぜこの国の影響力が12年後にこれほど大きくなるのかを言いました
because we at least
なぜなら私たちは少なくとも
If our policy is done well
私たちの政策がうまく行けば
all our parents
私たちの両親全員
If you brighten his thoughts and eyes
彼の考えと目を輝かせたら
maybe we can cultivate
もしかしたら栽培できるかもしれない
What we call in educational terms
教育用語で言うところの
Make it Metascale
メタスケールにする
Metagability
メタビリティ
so-called metacapabilities
所謂的後設能力
What is meta-capability
メタケイパビリティとは何ですか
That is to say, I can activate the ability of knowledge
つまり知識能力を発動できる
I can activate the ability in my brain knowledge
脳内知識で能力を発動できる
For example, your communication skills
たとえば、コミュニケーション能力
your ability to read
あなたの読む能力
your inquiry skills
あなたの探究スキル
right
右
wait for these abilities
これらの能力を待ってください
Opportunities that can be cultivated in the future
将来に向けて開拓できるチャンス
should be more
もっとあるべきです
Of course there is a very important premise
もちろん大事な前提があります
we must make good use of
私たちはそれを上手に活用しなければなりません
extra three years
さらに3年
Make an overall plan for the whole course
コース全体の全体計画を立てる
I hope that within nine years
9年以内にそうなることを願っています
cultivate these abilities
これらの能力を養う
Absolutely better than you to cultivate Guoying's learning achievements in natural mathematics
Guoying の自然数学における学習成果を伸ばすには、あなたよりも絶対に優れています。
This manpower is more important
この人材の方が重要です
I think this is our big government
これが私たちの大きな政府だと思います
if you can see this
これを見ることができれば
maybe the twelve kingdoms
たぶん十二王国
It is really important for the future development of Taiwan
台湾の将来の発展にとって非常に重要です
is a very important opportunity
とても重要な機会です
That's because people today may come from many different places
それは、今日の人々はさまざまな場所から来た可能性があるからです
so i assume
だから私は推測します
Try to use more common
もっと一般的なものを使ってみてください
In a relatively unprofessional way
比較的非専門的な方法で
let's talk about this topic
この話題について話しましょう
then if there is any question
それで何か質問があれば
we can discuss
話し合うことができます
let me share
共有させてください
that information is in the educational app itself
その情報は教育アプリ自体に含まれています
There are several tasks and goals
いくつかのタスクと目標があります
Finally, we hope to continue to do
最後に、私たちはこれからも続けていきたいと思っています
also hope to be able to complete
また完成できることを願っています
First
初め
The first of our learning journey
私たちの学習の旅の最初
throughout the learning process
学習プロセス全体を通して
How we use information technology
情報技術の使用方法
to help humans learn about human development
人間が人類の発達について学ぶのを助けるために
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
In fact everyone must have a progress in his learning process
実際、誰もが学習プロセスを進歩させなければなりません
Then in this learning process
そして、この学習プロセスでは
For example, if you study
たとえば勉強するとしたら
Is there any part in this course of study
このコースの読書の一部はありますか？
We can help through information technology
私たちは情報技術を通じてお手伝いできます
come to help you and can develop some of your academic and reading skills
あなたを助けに来て、学力と読解力を伸ばすことができます
Now an obvious example is ebooks
わかりやすい例は電子書籍です
I think everyone knows about e-books
電子書籍は皆さんご存知かと思いますが、
Whether it is the iPad or our domestic manufacturers
iPadでも国内メーカーでも
Epad is also good
エパッドもいいですね
The era of e-books has really come
本格的に電子書籍の時代が到来
but where is the problem now
しかし今どこに問題があるのか
We now have an e-book for everyone
誰でも使える電子書籍が登場しました
But can he let us do in-depth homework reading?
しかし、彼は私たちに詳細な宿題の読書をさせてくれるでしょうか?
And the way we're designing e-books now
そして私たちが今行っている電子書籍の設計方法
All are using the Skin reading method
全員がスキンリーディング法を使用しています
What is the so-called skin reading
いわゆるスキンリーディングとは何ですか
general practice book
一般的な練習本
He can't help you draw the key points for the first e-book, right?
彼は最初の電子書籍の重要なポイントを描くのを手伝うことはできませんよね?
Then you can't write down your thoughts.
それでは、自分の考えを書き留めることはできません。
Like many of our books there are
私たちの書籍の多くと同様に、
Then there is a little activity, let you use your brain
次に、ちょっとしたアクティビティがあります。頭を使ってみましょう
it has none in it
それには何も入っていない
So in a stage of development like this
このような発展段階では
Will there be any sequelae on the liquid poison?
液体毒の後遺症はあるのでしょうか？
But whether this road will go, it will definitely go to Asia
でもこの道が行くかどうかは間違いなくアジアに行くだろう
but this way
しかし、この方法で
is there a good way
良い方法はありますか
channel it into the most important development of our learning human
それを私たちの学習する人間の最も重要な成長に導く
If you are watching when you were young, watch Jin Yong when you were young
若い頃に見てるなら、若い頃にジンヨン見て
maybe it doesn't matter
たぶんそれは関係ない
it doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
But if you read ordinary textbooks
でも普通の教科書を読むと
Read math, read English, read nature, etc.
数学を読む、英語を読む、自然を読むなど。
Let you know how to let you in the whole liquid poisoning process
液体中毒のプロセス全体に参加する方法を教えてください
Emphasis on learning workforce development
人材育成の学習に重点を置く
So in order to achieve this one
したがって、これを達成するには
That's obvious from the specifications of our e-book
それは電子書籍の仕様を見れば明らかです
to modify
変更する
That is, it must increase some
つまり、ある程度増加する必要があります
The functions related to the study of liquid poison put it in
液体毒の研究に関する機能を搭載
Well, there are already many groups doing this
まあ、すでに多くのグループがこれを行っています
you are working on this one
あなたはこれに取り組んでいます
Is it possible to come up with the specifications of a good e-book
良い電子書籍の仕様を考え出すことはできますか?
Then on the students' learning
次に生徒たちの学習について
it is helpful
役に立ちます
This is a part worth studying
これは勉強する価値のある部分です
Then in addition now
それではさらに今
In a competitive environment in the 21st century
21世紀の競争環境において
Because a recent statistic
最近の統計だから
in the twenty-first century
21世紀に
What kind of manpower will affect future competition
どのような人材が将来の競争に影響を与えるか
you personally will have an impact
あなた個人が影響を与えるでしょう
One of the most important is cooperative learning
最も重要なことの 1 つは協調学習です
a cooperative learning
協力的な学習
this used to be possible
これは以前は可能でした
We in Taiwan rarely pay attention to this
私たち台湾人はこのことをほとんど気にしません
We value personalization
私たちはパーソナライズを重視します
Is there any way we can cooperate with others
他の人と協力できる方法はありますか
Collaborate to solve common problems
よくある問題を解決するために協力する
You may need this one to enter the society
社会に出るにはこれが必要かも
The ability to cooperate
協力する能力
How to train the ability to cooperate
協力する力を鍛える方法
In the Internet age, it could have helped acting skills
インターネット時代なら演技力にも役立ったかもしれない
in a kaohsiung
高雄で
one in japan, one in america, one in taipei
日本に1つ、アメリカに1つ、台北に1つ
those four
あの4人
How can one work together to solve some problems through the Internet?
インターネットを通じて問題を解決するためにどのように協力できるでしょうか?
Networked Collaborative Learning Capabilities
ネットワーク化された共同学習機能
Or the ability to cooperate and solve problems together
または協力して問題を一緒に解決する能力
how to build it
どのように構築するか
So how can we help it in this process
では、このプロセスでどのように支援できるでしょうか
This is all in the whole training process
これはトレーニングプロセス全体のすべてです
A part of what we hope to be able to achieve
私たちが達成できることを期待していることの一部
so this is the first
これが最初です
Second, we hope to use the digitized eye of a fellow student
次に、他の学生のデジタル化された目を活用したいと考えています。
To enrich the experience of ability learning
能力学習の経験を豊かにするために
and learning methods to improve it
そしてそれを改善するための学習方法
this is very interesting
これはとても興味深いです
once there was a teacher
かつて先生がいた
a primary school teacher
小学校の先生
Then he wants students to find information through the Internet
そして、学生たちにインターネットを通じて情報を見つけてもらいたいと考えています。
and then make a report
そしてレポートを作成します
Then I remember his first topic
それから私は彼の最初の話題を思い出します
He wants elementary school students to organize a
彼は小学生たちにイベントを企画してほしいと考えています。
Life of a Butterfly
蝶の一生
Then I hope that after the students sort it out
それから生徒たちがそれを整理した後、私はそれを願っています
then find a report
それからレポートを見つけてください
After the result report came out, the teacher was very sad
結果報告が出た後、先生はとても悲しんでいました
Because everyone's homework is similar
宿題はみんな似ているから
Why? Because all use copy passed
なぜですか? すべてコピーが渡されたものを使用するためです。
All with copy passed and no bets
すべてコピーがパスされ、賭けはありません
students did not gamble
学生はギャンブルをしませんでした
So later he laughed at himself and said
それで後で彼は自分自身を笑いながら言いました
I was going to let them know that butterflies
私は彼らに蝶の存在を知らせるつもりだった
Turns out it only taught them the human power of the computer
結局のところ、それはコンピュータの人間力を教えただけだった
called copy passed
渡されたコピーと呼ばれる
Nothing else was taught
それ以外は何も教えられなかった
So Taiwanese teachers are also good.
なので台湾人の先生も良いです。
he will wake up
彼は目を覚ますでしょう
He'll think that's wrong
彼はそれは間違っていると思うだろう
this will be problematic
これは問題になるだろう
He later came up with another topic
彼は後で別の話題を思いついた
like the insect doctor
例：昆虫博士
But does he want students to read?
しかし、彼は生徒たちに本を読んでもらいたいのでしょうか？
So you're going to teach the insect doctor when the report comes out
報告書が出たら昆虫博士に教えることになるんですね
must focus
集中しなければなりません
You have to draw key points to be able to teach
教えるためには重要なポイントを引く必要がある
As a result, when he got it back, he was very sad again.
その結果、それを取り戻したとき、彼はまたとても悲しくなりました。
Why are you sad?
どうして悲しいの？
Because everyone wrote another trick called underline
みんながアンダーラインという別のトリックを書いたから
called underline, it will do nothing
アンダーラインと呼ばれますが、何もしません
that will do nothing
それは何もしないでしょう
So you see that computer tools do have a lot of sequelae
コンピューターツールには多くの副作用があることがわかります
Then later he thought
それから後で彼はこう思いました
he doesn't do that much
彼はそんなことはしません
I still can't read anything like this.
まだこんなものは読めません。
Originally identified as Baidu Film
当初はBaidu Filmとして特定されました
Learning by doing should be for students to learn by doing
実践による学習とは、生徒が実践によって学習するものであるべきです
The result is that the teacher does the middle school by himself
その結果、中学校は先生が一人でやることになった
Because he wants to distinguish the difference in nutritional work
栄養の働きの違いを区別したいため
And it's hard to separate
そして分離するのは難しい
Because everyone is similar
みんな似てるから
So he thought it was wrong
それで彼はそれは間違っていると思った
he wants to change the method
彼は方法を変えたいと思っています
he said that's good
彼はそれは良いと言いました
Don't use that word for this
この言葉にはその言葉を使わないでください
You just use Powerpoint
パワーポイントを使うだけです
don't write too much
あまり書かないでください
All in Powerpoint
すべてパワーポイントで
And he also stipulated that Powerpoint can only be five pages
また、パワーポイントは 5 ページまでであるとも規定しました。
right
右
and the focus of each page
そして各ページの焦点
his title
彼の称号
set the title
タイトルを設定する
Each bar below that has its own phone
その下の各バーには独自の電話番号があります
In fact, this is a change of concept
実はこれは概念の転換です
that is
あれは
In transaction theory there is a
トランザクション理論には、
phonetic writing
ふりがな
construction theory
構築理論
Constructive theory he has an emphasis on
彼が重視している建設理論
all knowledge
すべての知識
build by yourself
自分で構築する
what you want
あなたが欲しいもの
self-construction
自己構築
must give him a scaffold
彼に足場を与えなければならない
This is like we cover the yellow fish
これは黄色い魚をカバーするようなものです
give him the scaffold first
まず彼に足場を与えてください
After he wrote Ye Duo
Ye Duoを書いた後
The scaffolding needs to be removed slowly
足場はゆっくりと撤去する必要があります
So his homework is done with the concept of scaffolding
したがって、彼の宿題は足場の概念で完了しました
That is to say he brought up a lot of headlines
つまり、彼は多くの見出しを持ち出したということです
The title is just to tell the students
タイトルは生徒たちに伝えたいだけです
you follow the direction of this title
あなたはこのタイトルの方向性に従います
go find your material class
マテリアルクラスを見つけてください
This is a bit of belief
これはちょっとした信念です
human beings who believe in knowledge
知識を信じる人間
or this
またはこれ
As for Powerpoint, teachers don’t have to use it
パワーポイントについては、教師が使用する必要はありません
Students can also use
学生さんも利用できます
Students organize knowledge through Powerpoint
学生はパワーポイントを使用して知識を整理します
Where are the resources?
リソースはどこにありますか?
on the web
ウェブ上で
but we must also admit
しかし私たちはまた認めなければなりません
Too much information on the internet is wrong
ネット上の情報は間違っているものが多すぎる
right
右
and the most wrong
そして最も間違っているのは
I want to learn the scariest of the above
上記の中で最も怖いものを学びたい
will cause a lot of misconceptions
多くの誤解を引き起こすだろう
What is the concept of myth
神話の概念とは何ですか
It's just a false notion that you think you're right
自分が正しいと思うのは単なる誤った考えだ
essentially it's wrong
本質的にそれは間違っている
but you think you're right
でもあなたは自分が正しいと思っている
However, if myths and concepts are not rooted in childhood,
ただし、神話や概念が幼少期に根ざしていない場合は、
Sometimes growing up is hard
成長するのは難しいこともある
There is indeed such a lot of myths on the Internet
インターネット上には本当にたくさんの神話が存在します
if you don't teach your students
生徒に教えないと
It is very likely that students will step into the trap of knowledge
学生が知識の罠に陥る可能性が非常に高い
That myth must be rectified.
その通説は修正されなければなりません。
if not corrected back
修正し直さなかったら
big problem
大問題
You can do experiments when you go back.
帰ったら実験もできる。
We have been taught since childhood that
私たちは子供の頃からこう教えられてきました
what will happen to finger ye liang
フィンガー・イェリャンはどうなるのか
ears will fall off, right?
耳が落ちてしまいますよね？
right
右
is this right or wrong
これは正しいですか、それとも間違っていますか
wrong right wrong
間違った正しい間違った
Wait a minute and go back up to see if you dare to point
ちょっと待って、上に戻って、あえて指さすかどうかを確認してください
Many people really dare not point out
多くの人は本当に指摘する勇気がありません
we have done
私たちは物事をやり遂げました
Not only dare not point it out, but some point it out reluctantly
あえて指摘しないばかりか、嫌々指摘する人もいる
You will solve the strange ears
奇妙な耳を解決します
That myth concept is very complicated and difficult to reverse
その神話の概念は非常に複雑で、覆すのは困難です
So the sooner you get it all out
だから早く全てを出し切った方がいいよ
the reverse is better
逆の方が良い
It's smart to have a teacher
先生がいると賢いよ
he
他
he knows us
彼は私たちを知っています
There are a lot of mistakes on the Internet.
インターネット上には間違いがたくさんあります。
So he can't let Xiesheng look at it casually
だから謝生にそれを気軽に見させるわけにはいかない
He just had a homework
彼はちょうど宿題をしたところだ
that homework is very simple
その宿題はとても簡単です
So once one direction is changed, the whole will be changed
つまり、一方向が変われば全体が変わる
he has a website
彼はウェブサイトを持っています
There are many mistakes in it, and he will tell you
そこには間違いがたくさんある、そして彼はあなたに教えてくれるでしょう
There are many mistakes in it
間違いがたくさんあります
But you guys go online and find out what's wrong
でも君たちはオンラインにアクセスして何が問題なのか調べてみる
do you know what i mean
分かりますか
this is one
これは 1 つです
Use the words of the Internet to achieve the purpose of cooperation
協力の目的を達成するためにインターネットの言葉を使用する
This is a very simple method
これは非常に簡単な方法です
So like our digits are long
私たちの数字が長いように
Actually there is an important part
実は重要な部分がある
Taiwan has many precious things
台湾には貴重なものがたくさんある
We want to do something recently
最近やりたいことがあります
Of course it has its difficulty
もちろん難しさはありますが
For example, because
たとえば、次のような理由からです。
There's a lot of trouble being the principal at Shida University
志田大学の校長は大変だ
the most painful thing for me
私にとって最も苦痛なこと
Every time I go to the art exhibition
美術展に行くたびに
I really can't see some art exhibitions
いくつかの美術展は本当に見られない
There are some abstractions that I can't see either
私にも見えない抽象化がいくつかあります
don't know how to appreciate
感謝の仕方がわからない
so i was thinking
それで私は考えていました
if there is someone next to you
あなたの隣に誰かがいるなら
I have someone to accompany me to see
一緒に見てくれる人がいる
Then they are explaining this painting to me
それから彼らはこの絵を私に説明しています
how nice he is
彼はなんて素敵なんだろう
So I sometimes go to the boss of the art department
それで私は時々美術部の上司のところに行きます
teacher go together
先生も一緒に行きましょう
And every time they tell me
そして彼らが私に言うたびに
Just let you read the book by yourself
一人で本を読ませてください
oh
おお
because
なぜなら
because there are many abstractions
抽象化が多いので
oh
おお
But it's hard to explain
でも説明するのは難しい
Maybe my math literacy is too low
私の数学リテラシーが低すぎるのかもしれません
He didn't bother to explain to me
彼はわざわざ私に説明しようとしなかった
So I then thought of a question
それで私は質問を考えました
Is it possible for me?
私にも可能でしょうか？
is it possible
出来ますか
I took an iPad
iPadを持って行きました
He has a camera or an Epad camera
彼はカメラまたは Epad カメラを持っています
Then let's take a picture of this picture
じゃあこの写真を撮りましょう
After taking a picture, he will naturally
写真を撮った後、彼は自然に
Someone who will automatically have a commentary will run out
自動的に解説してくれる人が足りなくなる
then help me explain
それなら説明を手伝ってください
can it be done
できるでしょうか
sure
もちろん
Now this technology is called Augmented Reality.
現在、このテクノロジーは拡張現実と呼ばれています。
We are working on an agreement now
私たちは現在協定に取り組んでいます
right
右
like this
このような
Music is the same
音楽も同じだ
we listen to music every time
私たちは毎回音楽を聴きます
right
右
like this week
今週のように
me a week
私は一週間
I'm going to be forced to listen to music
強制的に音楽を聴かされることになる
Then every time you have to go to the first position
その後、毎回最初の位置に移動する必要があります
I say the first position
最初のポジションと言うのは
and put me in the fifth position
そして私を5位に置きました
so i saw you later and said
それで後で会ってこう言いました
not the first position
最初のポジションではない
What move do we have? Fifth position
どのような動きがあるでしょうか? 5 番目の位置
that's the same
それは同じです
you always have to understand
あなたは常に理解する必要があります
So we just want to say
だから私たちはただ言いたいのです
Is there any technology to help us look at the music industry?
音楽業界を見るのに役立つテクノロジーはありますか?
I don't use the listening industry, but the watching industry
私は聞く業界ではなく見る業界を利用します。
What do I use to take a picture and take a picture of it
写真を撮ったり、写真を撮ったりするには何を使用しますか
or after taking a picture
または写真を撮った後
it naturally explains to me
それは自然に私に説明してくれる
I explain a whole change this whole night
この一晩中、全体の変化を説明します
That's why I say technology can achieve this
だからこそ私はテクノロジーがこれを達成できると言っているのです
it is a secondary attack
それは二次攻撃です
Then in our digital content
そしてデジタルコンテンツで
There are actually a lot of works of art in the collection
実はコレクションにはたくさんの美術品があるんです
that's a lot of interesting stuff
それはとても興味深いことだ
that interesting thing
その興味深いこと
Can it become a learning eye?
学びの目になるのか？
How can this place be a family?
どうしてこの場所が家族になれるのでしょうか？
Let something die, a treasured thing
何かを死なせて、大切なものを
In the end, it becomes a living teaching material
やがて生きた教材となる
I think it's worth dealing with
対処する価値はあると思う
In addition, there is another
さらに、もう一つあります
whole learning technology
学習テクノロジー全体
Resources that can make our digital learning
デジタル学習を可能にするリソース
Can do sustainable use and development
持続可能な利用と開発ができる
I still can't think of how to use it
まだ使い方が思いつきません
after that you can't imagine
その後は想像もつかない
for example
例えば
in education technology
教育テクノロジーの分野で
The first was the personal computer
最初はパソコンでした
Then slowly developed into the Internet age
その後、インターネット時代へとゆっくりと発展していきました
Then the Internet age put
その後、インターネット時代が到来し、
place of acting
演的地方
Various people put it together
いろんな人がまとめてるんだよ
right
右
and then progress to mobile vehicles
そして移動車両に発展する
Now Yingduan Technology
今、営団テクノロジー
and then a variety of
そしてその後、さまざまな
The technology of information application is getting more and more advanced
情報活用技術はますます高度化しています
Then the e-book came again
そしてまた電子書籍が来た
Then the change function of the function of the camera is
するとカメラの機能の変更関数は
getting better and better
どんどん良くなっていきます
so sometimes say
だから時々言う
Although our resources
私たちのリソースですが、
Now we don't know how to use
今では使い方が分かりません
But maybe after a certain stage of technological development
しかし、おそらく技術開発の特定の段階の後では、
Its use comes naturally
その使用は自然に行われます
i just ran out
私はちょうど使い果たしました
But do you want a Suviva?
でも、あなたはSuvivaが欲しいですか？
Because Suviva can make us finer
スビバは私たちをより美しくしてくれるから
save that side
その側を保存してください
Then there will be a chance to use
そうすれば使う機会もあるだろう
Then there is another one
それからもう一つあります
Implementation of information education
情報教育の実施
Hope to improve the former
前者は改善してほしい
digital literacy
デジタルリテラシー
Of course now what we call
もちろん、今私たちが呼んでいるのは
Digital literacy does not mean how high your credit standing is
デジタル リテラシーは信用度の高さを意味するものではありません
right
右
You are not all...
あなたは全員ではありません...
not all citizens
国民全員ではない
write credit science
信用科学を書く
no
いいえ
Instead, use existing credit tools
代わりに、既存の信用ツールを使用してください
how to solve his problem
彼の問題をどうやって解決するか
solve his life problems
彼の人生の問題を解決する
solve his learning problems
彼の学習上の問題を解決する
This becomes increasingly important
これはますます重要になります
One training for one ability
1 つの能力に対して 1 つのトレーニングを行う
It's already booked
すでに予約されています
of course there is an audience
もちろん観客がいる
There are about six core competencies in digital literacy
デジタル リテラシーにはおよそ 6 つのコア コンピテンシーがあります
Six core competencies
6つのコアコンピテンシー
Each core competency has one
各コア コンピテンシーには 1 つあります
Various types of indicators
各種インジケーター
then we wish to say
それから私たちは言いたいのです
Future Credit Courses
将来の単位コース
From elementary school to university
小学校から大学まで
Of course, this is excluding the sacrifice of undergraduate credit department
もちろん、これには学部の単位取得部門の犠牲は含まれていません。
Is an ordinary student
普通の学生です
you are a law student
あなたは法学部の学生です
You are a student of the Chinese Department
あなたは中国語学科の学生です
Then what kind of credit quality should you keep in mind?
では、どのような信用の質を心がけるべきでしょうか？
this is
これは
is more and more important
ますます重要になっています
at least the first
少なくとも最初の
We saw
私たちは見た
After you take it, after you touch it
手に取った後、触れた後
You can use at least 50% or 60% of the functions
少なくとも 50% または 60% の機能を使用できます
Now children and students
今では子どもたちや学生さんも
Almost everything can be solved like this
ほとんどすべてがこれで解決できます
They also rarely read the manual
マニュアルもほとんど読まない
rarely read that manual
そのマニュアルをめったに読まない
like you hold a cell phone
携帯電話を持っているように
For the students, I don't think they will read the manual
学生にとってはマニュアルを読まないと思う
He takes it, touches it, hits it
彼はそれを受け取り、触れ、叩きます
That's the way we are, but we can't see it.
それが私たちの姿ですが、私たちにはそれが見えません。
And now we don't know what
そして今、私たちはそれが何なのかわかりません
Our Dean Wang Hu wrote the article
私たちのディーン・ワン・フーが記事を書きました
Our current Guowen ability seems to be relatively poor
現在のGuowenの能力は比較的低いようです
So that manual
それでそのマニュアルは
I don't know that the manual is influenced by politicians
マニュアルが政治家の影響を受けているとは知りません
because of jump thinking
ジャンプ思考のせいで
So what was written in the manual is really jumpy enough.
マニュアルに書かれていることは本当に飛びつきます
you really don't know what he's writing
彼が何を書いているのか本当にわかりません
right but it's weird
そうだけど変だよ
Why can't young people understand
なぜ若者には理解できないのか
we don't understand
私たちは理解できません
It may be that the result of the training is not the same
トレーニングの結果は同じではない可能性があります
That's rare. Now there are few such manuals.
今ではそのようなマニュアルはほとんどありません。
Almost you go online, you have to go online if you want to read the manual
ほとんどオンラインになりますが、マニュアルを読みたい場合はオンラインに接続する必要があります
The basic application ability will become more and more clear
基礎応用力がますます明確になる
Now what is our biggest concern for the next generation, you know?
私たちが今、次世代のために最も心配していることは何ですか？
cyber crime
サイバー犯罪
This is cybercrime is a serious problem
これはサイバー犯罪です、深刻な問題です
it's sometimes a temptation
それは時々誘惑です
Well, we have come across a few cases
さて、いくつかのケースに遭遇しました
It may be that our own education has not been done well.
私たち自身の教育が十分にできていないのかもしれません。
Then let the children really face legal problems
それから子供たちに実際に法的問題に直面させてください
especially at what stage
特にどの段階で
After high school
高校卒業後
And it just so happened that these students just retired
そして、たまたまその学生たちがちょうど退職したところです
push into the university
大学に押し込む
he already has school practice
彼はすでに学校の練習を受けています
But before entering the university formally, there may be
しかし、正式に大学に入学する前に、
three to four months or even half a year
3～4ヶ月、場合によっては半年くらい
Because of rejection, isn't he?
拒否されたからですよね？
He didn't just pass the exam, right?
彼はただ試験に合格しただけではありませんね?
so for a long time
だから長い間
But everyone ignores a lot
でもみんなかなり無視してる
So if there are any parents here
それで、もしここに両親がいたら
Children are very careful just at this stage
この段階だけでも子どもたちはとても慎重です
They just turned eighteen
彼らは18歳になったばかりです
Many children do not know
知らない子供も多い
in our law
私たちの法律では
18 is an adult
18は大人です
So they were bored for a while
それで彼らはしばらく退屈していました
often on the site
サイトでよくある
then do something you shouldn't do
それならやってはいけないことをする
they may find it interesting
彼らはそれが面白いと思うかもしれない
these suspects find it funny
これらの容疑者はそれが面白いと思う
He also thinks there's nothing wrong with it.
彼もそれは問題ないと考えている。
As a result
結果として
Because we have a lot of internet police
サイバー警察がたくさんいるから
It's over because of this
これのせいで終わった
these have the case
これらにはケースがあります
There are these cases
こういったケースもあります
But after he broke the law
しかし、彼が法律を破った後、
Also know that he is 18 years old
彼が18歳であることも知っています
he is an adult
彼は大人です
so this is unfair
だからこれは不公平だ
Then this part is what we want
この部分が私たちが望むものです
always pay attention
常に注意を払う
sometimes we see
時々私たちは見る
This problem with many cybercriminals
多くのサイバー犯罪者が抱えるこの問題
it hurts so much
とても痛いです
He didn't mean to commit a crime at all.
彼は犯罪を犯すつもりはまったくありませんでした。
like now we mentor graduate students
今のように私たちは大学院生を指導しています
Where is the most feared student
最も恐れられている生徒はどこですか
Our advisors are also scared
私たちのアドバイザーも怖がっています
Because copypad is so convenient
コピーパッドって便利だから
They often inadvertently violate intellectual property
意図せずして知的財産を侵害してしまうことがよくあります
there will be that phenomenon of plagiarism
盗作という現象が起こるだろう
I copied the letter, this has to be dealt with
手紙をコピーしました、これは対処しなければなりません
So I said, how to avoid cybercrime
そこで私は、サイバー犯罪を回避するにはどうすればよいかを言いました。
information literacy
情報リテラシー
very important part
非常に重要な部分
So this is also worthy of our discussion
したがって、これも議論する価値があります
Ok, so I put some applied themes
さて、応用テーマをいくつか入れてみました
make a very simple explanation
とても簡単な説明をする
First, the establishment and attack of digital learning environments
第一に、デジタル学習環境の構築と攻撃
We want to build a digital learning environment
デジタル学習環境を構築したい
Digital learning environments now probably have many
現在、デジタル学習環境には多くのものが存在すると考えられます。
E-Learning platform, E-Learning platform
Eラーニングプラットフォーム、Eラーニングプラットフォーム
Now the most popular is the future classroom
今一番人気は未来の教室
That is to say, the classroom in the future
つまり、未来の教室
full of a
いっぱいの
For example, touch screen, electronic pendulum
例：タッチスクリーン、電子振り子
There are various resources over there, right?
そこにはさまざまなリソースがありますよね？
How to do this teaching
この教えをどのように行うか
How to teach on this platform
このプラットフォームで教える方法
The teacher almost had to re-believe
先生はほとんど信じ直さなければならなかった
Faith how to use this platform
信仰 このプラットフォームの使い方
The content in it, how to design your teaching content
その内容、教育内容の設計方法
How to design, this must be considered
どのように設計するか、これを考慮する必要があります
there is another
もう一つの...がある
The current camp terminal in this digital platform
このデジタルプラットフォームの現在のキャンプターミナル
We often go to the camp to calculate
私たちは計算するためによくキャンプに行きます
Camp platform
キャンププラットフォーム
If the camp terminal platform is really complete, it will really affect
キャンプターミナルプラットフォームが本当に完成すれば、大きな影響を与えるでしょう
A problem with many education in Taiwan
台湾の多くの教育が抱える問題
For example, inside the camp
例えばキャンプ内では
many of his software
彼のソフトウェアの多くは
All belong to APP, this kind of software is not big
すべてAPPに属し、この種のソフトウェアは大きくありません
That software doesn't do much
そのソフトウェアはあまり機能しません
so later
だから後で
If this develops to a certain stage
これがある程度の段階まで発展すると
It is very likely that when you learn certain information through the camp terminal
キャンプターミナルを通じて何らかの情報を知ると、
fragments of your knowledge
あなたの知識の断片
This is a piece of knowledge
これは豆知識です
So is there any sequelae when this is a fragment?
では、これが破片だった場合、後遺症はあるのでしょうか？
A knowledge restructuring ability of students may be more important
学生の一種の知識再構成能力の方が重要かもしれない
more important
より重要
effects like this
このような効果
will be more and more
ますます多くなるでしょう
The trend of technological development is irreversible
技術開発の流れは不可逆的です
But in the whole process of technological development, it will cause the problem of technological hindrance
しかし、技術開発の全過程において、技術的障害の問題が発生します。
hinder the development of other fields
他の分野の発展を妨げる
Then we all have to pay attention to this, so the platform
次に、私たち全員がこれに注意を払う必要があるため、プラットフォームは
Then there is this platform because there is a platform
それから、プラットフォームがあるので、このプラットフォームがあります
So our study
それで私たちの研究は
Identification of the community
的認定 community
i learn to shoot
私は射撃を学びます
This human soul community always experiences
この人間の魂のコミュニティは常に経験します
So some teachers can use the human spirit community
つまり、一部の教師は人間の精神コミュニティを利用できる
Gather the power of many other students
多くの生徒の力を結集して
to tutor students
家庭教師の生徒たちへ
There is also doing
やってる事もあります
so well done
とてもよくやった
It really helps a lot
本当にとても助かります
but you can't do well
でもあなたはうまくできない
there may be many problems
多くの問題があるかもしれない
What kind of students does the Human Soul community treat?
Human Soul コミュニティはどのような学生を扱いますか?
very helpful
非常に役立ちます
This is a result of some research
これはある研究の結果です
Very helpful for the kind of shy student
内気な生徒にとっては非常に役立ちます
our often shy students
内気なことが多い私たちの生徒たち
He dare not interact with people
彼は人々と交流することを敢えてしない
He dare not ask a question
彼はあえて質問をしなかった
right
右
dare not express an opinion
あえて意見を言わない
But you through this kind of networking
しかし、あなたはこの種のネットワーキングを通じて
When the soul community
ソウルコミュニティのとき
Because he won't face to face
彼は対面しないから
face to face
面と向かって
he through the Internet
彼はインターネットを通じて
he can make a good interaction
彼は良いやりとりができる
make good interaction
良い交流をする
so this part
それでこの部分
From a certain point of view, his academic achievement will be improved
ある観点から見れば、彼の学力は向上するだろう
So have one like this
それで、このようなものを持ってください
So the establishment of this whole learning environment is
したがって、この学習環境全体の確立は、
more and more complicated
ますます複雑になる
and more and more
そしてますます
that now
那現在
In universities, like Normal University, there are about 60% of the teachers
師範大学などの大学では、教師の約60％がいます。
Multiple digital learning platforms
複数のデジタル学習プラットフォーム
But digital learning platforms are not the only ones
しかし、デジタル学習プラットフォームだけではありません
which means we teach
つまり、私たちが教えるということです
The interaction between people is still very important
やはり人と人との交流は大切ですね
we can't ignore
私たちは無視できません
A brainstorming question between people
人々の間でのブレーンストーミングの質問
Not only through the Internet platform
インターネットプラットフォームだけでなく
So now the network platform has slowly developed into
現在、ネットワーク プラットフォームはゆっくりと発展してきました。
A study of the so-called Blenderland powder layer
いわゆるブレンダーランドパウダー層の研究
at a certain stage
ある段階で
There must be a face-to-face communication between the teacher and the students
教師と生徒の間には対面でのコミュニケーションが必要です
Internet-based processing at some stages of learning
学習のいくつかの段階でのインターネットベースの処理
For example, let me squeeze an example
たとえば、例を挙げてみましょう
Let's talk about the relationship between the nine planets and the sun
9つの惑星と太陽の関係について話しましょう
The relationship between the nine planets and the sun
9つの惑星と太陽の関係
We know that the earth rotates and revolves
私たちは地球が自転と公転をしていることを知っています
But this is very abstract
しかし、これは非常に抽象的です
very abstract for students
学生にとっては非常に抽象的
So how do you take the abstraction and turn it into
では、抽象化をどのようにして次のようなものに変換するのでしょうか。
I can do it easily through the computer
パソコンで簡単にできるよ
Otherwise you have to make an actual model
それ以外の場合は実際のモデルを作成する必要があります
I let the students watch
生徒たちに見てもらいました
I'll use a simpler example
より簡単な例を使用します
There is a teacher in our school
私たちの学校には先生がいます
I heard that he used to teach like this
こんな風に教えていたと聞いた
I'm of course taking the simpler example
もちろん、もっと単純な例を取り上げます
Let's say you teach that kindergarten student
あなたがその幼稚園児を教えているとしましょう
Then you have to teach what a pig is
それなら豚とは何かを教えなければなりません
right
右
It is very likely that students do not
学生はそうしない可能性が高い
he has never seen a pig
彼は豚を見たことがない
so pigs may be very abstract to him
だから彼にとって豚はとても抽象的なのかもしれない
right
右
It is very memorable for the teacher
先生にとってもとても思い出深いものです
You said this pig is very memorable
この豚はとても思い出深いとあなたは言いました
But it is very abstract for students
しかし学生にとっては非常に抽象的です
he may not know what a pig is
彼は豚が何なのか知らないかもしれない
how do you teach
どのように教えますか
so sometimes the best way
だから時々最善の方法
just do what you teach
教えられたことをただやるだけ
Then the teacher plays the pig for the students to see
それから先生は生徒たちに見てもらうために豚の役を演じます
it becomes a memory
それは思い出になる
is that impossible
それは不可能ですか
impossible
不可能
So through multimedia
そこでマルチメディアを通じて
I help you through online multimedia
オンラインマルチメディアを通じてお手伝いします
So something like this
それで、このようなもの
It's because he used to have a teacher named psychology
それは彼に心理学という先生がいたからです
he often talks
彼はよく話します
A Mental Change in the Monkey
猿の精神的変化
So I often play the role of a monkey for sacrifices
だから私はよく生贄の猿の役を演じる
right, that will make it clearer
そうです、それはより明確になります
so something like this
だからこのようなもの
Not many teachers like that know how to sacrifice
犠牲を払う方法を知っているそのような教師は多くありません
So what do you do, you have to do it through Domati
それでどうするかというと、Domati を通じて行う必要があります。
let the computer sacrifice
コンピュータに犠牲を与えましょう
Something like this, so the computer itself has a
このようなものなので、コンピューター自体には
A very important part is
非常に重要な部分は、
what can he play poses
彼はどんなポーズをとれるの？
Valence's role
ヴァランスの役割
You mean the gestures and voices he plays through the computer
つまり、彼がコンピューターを通じて演奏するジェスチャーや声のことです。
Some abstract ideas that make sacrifices clearer
犠牲をより明確にするいくつかの抽象的なアイデア
better understanding of abstract concepts
抽象的な概念をより深く理解する
Then it can be built on this platform
このプラットフォーム上で構築できます
Another one is
もう一つは、
tools for learning activities
学習活動のためのツール
Now we have to develop a lot of learning activities
これからはたくさんの学習活動を展開しなければなりません
Many things, what we call
多くのこと、私たちが呼んでいるもの
Editing tools for All-Sold-In-Two textbooks
2 冊売りの教科書の編集ツール
Editing tools for learning activities
学習活動のための編集ツール
Then how to design this
では、これをどうやってデザインするかというと、
We call it the intersectional design tool
私たちはこれを交差点デザインツールと呼んでいます
how do you script
どのようにスクリプトを作成しますか
Lesson plan How to integrate with resources on the Internet
授業計画 インターネット上のリソースと統合する方法
Integrate it, an evolution of this tool
このツールの進化版である統合
There are also interfaces and tools that facilitate human-computer interaction
人間とコンピュータの相互作用を促進するインターフェースやツールもあります
this is very important this current development
これは現在の開発において非常に重要です
more and more complicated more and more complicated
ますます複雑 ますます複雑
I was talking about augmented reality, right?
私は拡張現実について話していましたよね?
take reality take your real reality
現実を受け入れてください あなたの本当の現実を受け入れてください
Then amplify it with some information
何らかの情報でそれを増幅する
that you can achieve better human-machine interaction
そうすれば、人間とコンピューターのより良い相互作用を実現できます。
Then there's that mental reality, too.
それから、精神的な現実もあります。
If you watch TV or watch movies
テレビを見たり映画を見たりすると
you brought a universe
あなたは宇宙をもたらしました
When you stretch in the universe
あなたのいわゆる宇宙への伸びのとき
into the computer world
コンピューターの世界へ
then you act as an electron
そうすればあなたは電子として行動します
or act as a computer's current
またはコンピュータの電流として機能します
find information everywhere
あらゆる場所で情報を見つける
attract that reality
その現実を引き寄せる
It's all about the human-machine interface.
すべてはヒューマン マシン インターフェイスに関するものです。
But where is the big problem of the man-machine interface now?
しかし、マンマシンインターフェースの大きな問題は今どこにあるのでしょうか?
Currently very troublesome three drops
現在非常に厄介な3ドロップ
I have three drops now
今は3滴あります
Why is three drops so troublesome
なぜ3滴がそんなに面倒なのか
If you don't usually touch three drops
普段3滴触れない方は
if you just watch the three drops movie
スリードロップスの映画を見るだけなら
There are a lot of people who really get dizzy
本当にめまいがする人が多い
I really do
本当です
Because we have never had such a belief since childhood
私たちは子供の頃からそのような信念を持ったことがないからです
And the three drops themselves
そして3つのドロップ自体
often when not handled well
うまく扱われていない場合によくあること
There will also be learning disabilities
学習障害も出るだろう
there will be learning
学びがあるだろう
you just can't concentrate
あなたはただ集中できないだけです
i can't focus at all
全然集中できない
Similar to this problem came out
これと同じような問題が出てきました
don't say anything
何も言わないでください
do this briefing
このブリーフィングをする
It's easy for me to do this briefing, isn't it?
この説明会は私にとっては簡単ですよね。
someone does this briefing
誰かがこのブリーフィングをする
In order to increase the effect of human-computer interaction
人間とコンピュータのインタラクション効果を高めるために
Then there's a butterfly flying around
すると蝶が飛び回っています
right
右
effect?
効果？
and every time it comes out
そしてそれが出てくるたびに
The word "it" is used to run in.
「it」という言葉は走り込むために使われます。
Is it this way
こうですか
then sometimes
それから時々
Then one more word fell down
それからまた一つ言葉が落ちた
so again
それでまた
the scariest thing is
一番怖いのは
When the word fell down, there was still that killer body
言葉が落ちたとき、そこにはまだあの殺人者の死体があった
right
右
isn't it scary
怖くないですか
I see a lot of teachers in the past
過去にたくさんの先生に会ってきました
Just started to be a self-confident farmer
自信を持って農家になり始めたばかり
Those teachers will be scolded by me
あの先生たちは私に叱られるでしょう
why did i say two hours
なぜ2時間と言ったのですか
or after two hours of class
または2時間の授業後
You still have this kind of display.
まだこのような表示が残っていますね。
Then there is that word running down
それからあの言葉が流れてくる
And kill the car
そして車を殺します
I said it's no wonder that student didn't go crazy
私は、あの生徒が気が狂わなかったのは不思議ではないと言いました
Really, you can try it
本当に、試してみることができます
right
右
really going crazy
本当におかしくなる
and more multimedia
その他のマルチメディア
more severe cognitive load
より重度の認知負荷
What does cognitive load mean
認知負荷とはどういう意味ですか
because we have a short-term memory
私たちは短期記憶を持っているので、
that short term memory
その短期記憶
At the same time, the information that can be accepted is limited
同時に受け入れられる情報も限られている
if you take many words at the same time
同時に多くの単語を取得した場合
that's going to be a problem
それは問題になるだろう
then i will
それなら私がします
why butterflies
なぜ蝶なのか
what does this butterfly have to do with this
この蝶はこれと何の関係があるのですか
why do you want a butterfly to fly around
なぜ蝶を飛び回らせたいのですか
disturb us
私たちを邪魔します
right
右
really capable
本当に有能な
There are only two commonly used media
一般的に使用されるメディアは 2 つだけです
One is called vision and the other is called hearing
1つは視覚と呼ばれ、もう1つは聴覚と呼ばれます
right
右
Then the vision comes in and goes to the short-term memory of the vision
次に、ビジョンが入ってきて、そのビジョンの短期記憶に移ります。
When hearing comes in, it goes to auditory short-term memory
聴覚が入ってくると、聴覚の短期記憶に行きます。
These two signals must interact
これら 2 つの信号は相互作用する必要があります
an interaction
相互作用
Then if after the interaction
インタラクションの後であれば
you'll put the result in long-term memory
結果を長期記憶に残します
then you write something
それからあなたは何かを書きます
but we are not now
しかし、私たちは今はそうではありません
Look at our multimedia
当社のマルチメディアをご覧ください
That you look doesn't match your voice
見た目と声が合ってない
The two have no way to interact
二人には対話の余地がない
At the same time you are viewing too much data at the same time
同時に表示しているデータが多すぎます
There are animations, texts, and pictures
アニメーション、テキスト、写真があります
The same picture is presented for you to see
同じ写真が表示されますので、ご覧ください
So that all caused serious after-effects.
そのため、すべてが深刻な後遺症を引き起こしました。
really all distractions
本当にすべての気晴らし
You can do experiments when you go back.
帰ったら実験もできる。
This multimedia experiment is scary
このマルチメディア実験は恐ろしい
For example, if you drive a car, one day you will be able to drive
たとえば、車を運転するなら、いつかは運転できるようになるでしょう。
we have men who can drive
うちには運転できる男性がいます
Then you ask your wife to fish for you by the side
それからあなたは妻にそばで魚を釣るように頼みます。
How much did the stock drop today?
今日の株価はいくら下がりましたか？
I don't believe traffic will be safe
交通が安全になるとは思えない
Thanks
ありがとう
disturbed
邪魔された
because you see
あなたが見るから
road condition
道路状況
inconsistent with what your wife said
奥さんの言っていることと矛盾する
right
右
there will be problems
問題が起こるだろう
Let's squeeze another example why we punish students
なぜ学生を罰するのか、別の例を考えてみましょう
Now when students are punished, they are often accused, right? I just learned
今、生徒が罰を受けるとき、彼らは告発されることが多いですよね？今知りました
Why do you punish students for moving around and the defendant is sometimes sued by parents and children
なぜ学生の移動を罰するのか、被告は親子から訴えられることもある
Is it true that the private relationship has not been done well?
人間関係がうまくいっていないというのは本当ですか？
So it's very simple to punish students, don't scold him, don't beat him
したがって、生徒を罰するのは非常に簡単です。叱ったり、殴ったりしないでください。
I will change Mr. Hu
私が胡さんを変えます
Strong and bad all in white
強いものも悪いものもすべて白でまとめられている
Right? Then the student stood there and all he saw was white.
そうでしょう? すると学生はそこに立っていましたが、目に映るのは真っ白でした。
Then you just sit in front and give him two hours
それからあなたはただ前に座って彼に2時間与えてください
I can't see the skinny
痩せて見えない
Right? What he saw was completely inconsistent with what he heard.
そうでしょう? 彼が見たものは聞いたことと完全に一致しませんでした。
what's the use of hitting him
彼を殴って何の役に立つの？
Because you beat a student, he is young and he can recover easily
生徒を殴ったのだから、彼は若くて立ち直りやすい
Right? Then you are older, your cells after beating him
そうでしょう？彼を倒した後の細胞は年をとっています
and easy
そして簡単
lost
失った
Then your students are all recovered
そうすれば生徒たちは全員回復します
so you just don't
だからあなたはそうしないだけです
I'll just find a room called Fukushima City
福島市という部屋を探します
Do not stick anything on the long arm
長いアームには何も貼らないでください
Give him 70% white
彼に70％白を与えてください
But what he saw was a white wall
でも彼が見たのは白い壁だった
Then you talk to him about the things he's least interested in.
次に、彼が最も興味のないことについて話します。
After talking to him for an hour and two hours
彼と1時間、2時間話した後、
His ears create a cognitive load
彼の耳は認知負荷を生み出します
That's serious. You can try it when you go back.
それは大変なことです。戻ったら試してみてください。
So parents can do the same
だから親も同じことができる
we have kids, right?
私たちには子供がいますよね？
you teach your parents
あなたは両親に教えます
make a kitchen with you
あなたと一緒にキッチンを作りましょう
guaranteed to be fun
楽しいことは保証されています
So there are really many tools that can be researched here.
したがって、ここでは調査できるツールが本当にたくさんあります。
really a lot
本当にたくさん
One piece of information you can explore is a lot
1 つの情報で調べられるものはたくさんあります
I remember my son is very old now
私の息子はもうかなり大きくなったのを覚えています
we come back as soldiers
私たちは兵士として戻ってきます
I remember when he was in elementary school
彼が小学生の頃を思い出します
The elementary school was just doing that new dish
小学校ではちょうどその新しい料理をやっていたところだった
To see what's new
新機能を確認するには
So to practice new disk
新しいディスクを練習するために
Then we know that living in Taipei City
それから私たちは台北市に住んでいることを知ります
can you see the stars at night
夜に星が見えますか
can't see it
見えない
so i remember
だから覚えています
to do his homework
彼の宿題をするために
Then drive to that farm road in Keelung
それから基隆のあの農道まで車で行きます
Isn't there a farm road by the sea in Keelung?
基隆の海沿いに農道があるじゃないですか。
farm road and then
農道、そしてそれから
Use the horoscope chart with him to see various constellations
彼と一緒にホロスコープチャートを使ってさまざまな星座を見てみましょう
various constellations
各種星座
After reading it, you must go at night
読んだら夜に行くべし
So when I got home, it was like 3 or 4 o'clock
それで家に帰ったのは3時か4時くらいでした
I really want to sleep like this
本当はこのまま寝たい
As a result, my son woke me up at 7 o'clock in the morning
その結果、息子は朝7時に私を起こしました
his dad sucks shit what...what did i say shit
彼のお父さんはクソだ、何...私は何と言っただろうか
This is a constellation in the northern hemisphere, what about the southern hemisphere?
これは北半球の星座ですが、南半球ではどうでしょうか？
i just want
ただ欲しい
What is the best teaching? Contextualized teaching?
最良の教育とは何ですか? 状況に応じた教育とは何ですか?
Right, go directly to the scene?
そうだ、現場に直行するか？
But how did you get to the southern hemisphere?
しかし、どうやって南半球に到達したのでしょうか？
It's hard, isn't it?
大変ですね。
So sometimes the textbook is really badly designed, right?
教科書のデザインが本当にひどい場合もありますよね？
You can teach the northern hemisphere, but you are still teaching the southern hemisphere
北半球を教えることはできますが、依然として南半球を教えていることになります。
And our parents don't know what to do
そして私たちの両親は何をすればいいのか分かりません
It's even more hateful. What kind of course is there?
さらに憎たらしいのですが、どんなコースがあるのでしょうか？
Then watch the volcano explode.
それから火山が爆発するのを見てください。
Watching volcanic explosions, you need situational teaching
火山の爆発を観察するには、状況に応じた指導が必要です
don't know how...how to teach
どうやって...どうやって教えればいいのかわからない
Why...why can't you take him to the next seat to have a look?
どうして...なぜ彼を隣の席に連れて行って見てもらえないのですか?
So sometimes our situational teaching is
ですから、私たちが状況に応じて教えることがあるのは、
very good...both good teaching effect
非常に良い...両方とも良い教育効果
but often not feasible
しかし、多くの場合は実現不可能です
Of course not feasible
もちろん実現不可能
Like I know you are in elementary school and junior high school
あなたは小学生か中学生だと思います
When you were in junior high school, did you observe your karma when you were in elementary school?
中学生のとき、小学生のときの自分のカルマを観察しましたか？
Is there, is there, right?
あります、ありますよね？
Every child must observe the karma
すべての子供はカルマを観察しなければなりません
But at that time everyone had neck problems
でも当時は誰もが首に問題を抱えていた
Just look up and look again, causing traffic problems again
上を向いてまた見て、また交通問題を引き起こす
right? what should I do?
そうですか？どうすればいいですか？
But where can you find the karma for 365 days a year?
しかし、1年365日のカルマはどこで見つけられるのでしょうか？
Are there any on the Internet? Yes, really.
インターネット上に何かありますか? はい、そうです。
A karma simulation of 365 days during that period
その間の365日のカルマシミュレーション
so many teachers find that site
非常に多くの教師がそのサイトを見つけます
Then give a lot of homework and ask them to analyze the changes in the entire karma
次に、たくさんの宿題を出し、カルマ全体の変化を分析するように依頼します。
This is the idea of ​​constructivism
これが構成主義の考え方です
He doesn't tell you the answer
彼は答えを教えてくれません
Tell you to look at various karma to find out some relationships
関係性を見つけるためにさまざまなカルマを調べるように言います
So this is a lot, actually the human interface
これは実際にはヒューマンインターフェイスです
Very helpful for contextualized communication
状況に応じたコミュニケーションに非常に役立ちます
very helpful that works well
とても役に立ちます、うまくいきます
But I have a lot of opinions, every time I talk to some teachers
でも、先生たちと話すたびに、たくさんの意見があります。
They are not willing to accept my good words
彼らは私の良い言葉を素直に受け入れようとしない
In fact, there are several examples
実際にいくつかの例があります
We often teach children
私たちはよく子供たちに教えます
If you meet Shero
シェロに会えたら
How should it be, right?
それはどうあるべきですか？
So the teacher will want to say on the blackboard
だから先生は黒板にこう言いたいだろう
when you meet the bad guys or the club
悪者やクラブに出会ったとき
what do you want first
最初に何が欲しいですか
what about the second one
2番目はどうですか
What about the third one?
3番目はどうでしょうか？
Is it like this
こんな感じかな
But really, if one day we meet
でも本当に、いつか会えたら
what will happen to this student
この生徒はどうなるでしょうか
nothing can happen
何も起こらない
Because he cuts out the chance to practice
練習の機会を奪われるから
right
右
But is this kind of practice possible for him?
しかし、このような練習は彼に可能でしょうか？
no way
とんでもない
how can you get these people to practice
どうすればこの人たちに練習してもらえるでしょうか？
Come back after practicing once
一度練習してから戻ってきてください
So I talked to many
それで色々な人と話しました
The middle school sex director said
中学校の性指導者はこう言った。
Isn't our school building a lot of nature trails?
私たちの学校は自然遊歩道をたくさん作っているのではないでしょうか？
the learning trail
学習の道
Just as I said, why don't you make a club
先ほども言ったように、クラブを作ってみませんか？
Then let the general
それなら将軍に任せましょう
Let the sex director play the role of the club man
セックスディレクターにクラブマンの役割を果たしてもらいましょう
Give students the opportunity to practice
生徒たちに練習の機会を与える
right
右
How good is it to achieve the purpose of situational teaching
状況に応じた教育の目的を達成することがどれほど良いか
But they don't seem to want
でも彼らは望んでいないみたいだ
stay away from my opinion
私の意見から離れてください
I think I'm still strong
まだ強いと思う
this opinion is good
この意見は良いです
But they are not willing to accept
しかし、彼らは受け入れるつもりはありません
very strange
非常に奇妙な
I said, then you take turns to do it.
私は言いました、じゃあ順番にやってください。
Don't trust the old director every time, right?
毎回昔の監督を信用するわけにはいかないですよね？
You Lutheran Lord can do it too.
ルーテル教会の主であるあなたにもそれができます。
there is another
もう一つの...がある
Learning without Hu Shou
胡寿なしで学ぶ
This study without Hu Shou is a
胡寿抜きのこの研究は、
Future development because we learn from the effectiveness
効果から学ぶからこその今後の展開
There are probably formal learning and informal learning
おそらくフォーマルな学習とインフォーマルな学習があるでしょう
A kind of learning like school belongs to formal learning
学校のような一種の学習は正式な学習に属します
But informal learning is like a museum
しかし、非公式の学習は博物館のようなものです
Moreover, in our general learning environment,
さらに、私たちの一般的な学習環境では、
about seventy or eighty percent
70パーセントか80パーセントくらい
It's all about informal learning
それはすべて非公式な学習に関するものです
will formally learn about
について正式に学びます
But I will study formally
でも正式に勉強します
For example, if you go to a museum to visit
たとえば、美術館に行って見学する場合、
can you really learn about all the artifacts in the museum
博物館内のすべての工芸品について本当に学ぶことができますか
can you help me
手伝って頂けますか
So what do we often do
それで、私たちはよく何をしますか
Will find a guide's energy to assist us, right?
私たちを助けてくれるガイドのエネルギーを見つけてくれるでしょう?
action learning now
今すぐアクションラーニング
This has its advantage
これには利点があります
Have it to bring your navigating energy to you
ナビゲーションのエネルギーをもたらしてくれるでしょう。
bring you
あなたに持ってくる
I bring you to deal with
対処するために連れてきます
that same same
同じ同じ
Like that learning walk, I often say that there are many learning walks in schools now
その学習ウォークと同じように、今学校では学習ウォークがたくさんあるとよく言います。
The learning trail can also be used as a mobility vehicle
学習コースは移動手段としても使用可能
integrated into the learning trail
学習トレイルに統合される
you got somewhere
あなたはどこかに行きました
He will show you some relevant information
彼はあなたにいくつかの関連情報を示します
Now in many elementary schools
今では多くの小学校で
Isn't there an outdoor teaching association?
野外指導協会ってないんですか？
Doesn't the Outdoor Education Association have a study list? Right?
野外教育協会には検討リストはありませんか?
In the study sheet, there is a principle in the design of the study sheet
学習シートには、学習シートのデザインに原則があります。
He hopes that through the topics in the worksheet
彼は、ワークシートのトピックを通じて、
To guide you to explore some information on the site
サイト上の情報を探索するためのガイドとして
Explore some plants in your outdoor teaching association as well
屋外教育協会でも植物を探索しましょう
animals too , i hope you explore
動物たちも、ぜひ探検してみてください
So the design of that topic is very important
したがって、そのトピックのデザインは非常に重要です
but in this whole
しかし、この全体の中で
in the process of exploring
探索の過程で
For example, you read a page
たとえば、あるページを読んだとします。
If the student doesn't understand, he doesn't understand
生徒が理解できないなら、彼は理解していない
Because there are no information stations hidden in this page
このページには隠された情報ステーションがないため、
Can you understand what I mean? The page you read is just a page
意味がわかりますか? あなたが読んでいるページはただのページです
Does it have any information in it?
何か情報が入っているのでしょうか？
What if you go through a mobile vehicle
移動車両を通過したらどうなるか
situational awareness
状況認識
What does situational awareness mean?
状況認識とは何を意味しますか
when it gets there it will
そこに着いたらそうなります
Survive to sense
生き残って感覚を身につける
After sensing it, it will take you this
感知した後、これを受け取ります
Information about this leaf
この葉っぱの情報
will show up on your screen
画面に表示されます
just provide some additional information
追加情報を提供するだけです
additional information to help
役立つ追加情報
So something like this
それで、このようなもの
So it is very suitable for use in informal learning
そのため、非公式な学習での使用に非常に適しています
Also in formal learning
正式な学習でも
also a very important
また非常に重要な
in trading theory
トレーディング理論では
inside the trading theory
トレーディング理論の内側
Our Hirara
私たちの平良
There are two types of Hira
ヒラには2種類ある
one called
呼ばれた人
One type of formation Taira
一種形成性平良
summative level
総和レベル
What does formative goodness mean?
形成的善とはどういう意味ですか？
that is
あれは
I hope that after this formative Hira
この形成的なヒラが終わったらいいなと思います
Know what your current study status is
現在の学習状況を知る
Then according to your study status
あとは学習状況に応じて
I will do remedial teaching
補習をさせていただきます
I am formative Hirao
造形平尾です
That summative level
その総括的なレベル
So it’s because the pedestrian Xingping Liang is a very important role for half a year
したがって、歩行者の梁星平は半年の間非常に重要な役割を果たします。
But we're almost in a classroom in Taiwan
でも、私たちはもうすぐ台湾の教室にいます
Hirao
平尾
why? we have a lot of quizzes
なぜですか? クイズがたくさんあります
Right? But after the quiz
そう?でもクイズの後は
Does any teacher have time to read the results of the quiz
クイズの結果を読む時間のある教師はいますか
Then judge which concept in the previous class is not understood
次に、前のクラスのどの概念が理解できていないかを判断します
He can only do well in the previous class
彼は前のクラスでしか成績が良くない
What is your average grade?
あなたの平均成績は何ですか
He has no way to judge which concept in the previous class is not understood
彼には、前の授業のどの概念が理解されていないのかを判断する方法がありません。
Because the teacher has no time
先生は時間がないので
So we only have quizzes
だからクイズしかない
We take the quiz as a summative level
クイズは総括レベルとして取り上げます
so in the classroom
それで教室で
If people, teachers, real people
もし人々が、教師が、本物の人々が
With the teaching mode like this with students
生徒たちとこんな感じのティーチングモードで
There is probably no way to be a pedestrian
おそらく歩行者になる方法はありません
That is to say, there is almost no way for the teacher to know
つまり、先生には知る由がほとんどないのです。
Which classmate or most of the classmates in the previous class
前のクラスのクラスメート、またはほとんどのクラスメート
which idea is not understood
どの考えが理解されないのか
There's almost no way I can be pedestrian
歩行者になることはほぼ不可能です
there is almost no way i can do it
私にできる方法はほとんどありません
that's an important part
それは重要な部分です
Then this mobile vehicle can do that
この移動車両ならそれができます
because it can drop the title where
なぜなら、タイトルをどこにでもドロップできるからです。
Throw it into every man's mobile vehicle
すべての人の移動車両に放り込んでください
students can answer
学生は答えることができます
Immediately after answering, collect them all
答えたらすぐに全部回収する
Can do data processing
データ処理ができる
can judge immediately
すぐに判断できる
Which idea does the student not understand
学生が理解できない考えはどれですか
you will fix it next time
次回はそれを修正します
do remedial this instructable
これを修正してください
like this
このような
So this place can improve us a kind
だからこの場所は私たちを少し改善してくれる
A practice of Comoron Forest
コモロの森の実践
like a museum is not real
博物館が現実ではないように
when you visit a museum
美術館を訪れるとき
For example, we sometimes receive this
たとえば、こんなことをいただくことがあります。
What is the characteristic of this management
この経営の特徴は何ですか
which dynasty
どの王朝
And what kind of special love story is there on his front?
そして彼の前にはどんな特別なラブストーリーがあるのでしょうか？
But one of the most important features of this management
しかし、この管理の最も重要な特徴の 1 つは、
is behind
後ろにいる
Do we now have a master that will automatically
現在、自動的に実行するマスターはありますか?
turn around to show you
振り向いてあなたに見せてください
Won't
しません
right
右
So you pass through the mobile vehicle
それであなたは移動車両を通過します
information behind
背後にある情報
render it into your vehicle
それをあなたの車両にレンダリングします
So a kind of mobility vehicle
つまりモビリティの一種
action learning
アクションラーニング
A very important part of this part is
この部分の非常に重要な部分は、
human muscle
人間の筋肉
skin
肌
on the actual situation
実際の状況について
The interaction of the three brings it together
三人の掛け合いが一つに繋がる
integrate it
それを統合する
this is the hardest part
これが最も難しい部分です
from a transactional point of view
トランザクションの観点から
How do we muscle people
どうやって人を筋肉質にするのか
The three put it together
3人でまとめました
it's difficult
それは難しい
How are you framing this transaction scenario?
この取引の状況をどのように捉えていますか?
so this place will
だからこの場所は
there is another one
もう一つあります
Hu Shou is not in a learning digital content communication strategy and Pingliang method will change
学習デジタルコンテンツのコミュニケーション戦略と平涼メソッドは胡寿なしで変わる
because your screen is not big
画面が大きくないので
right so you can render the content at the same time
コンテンツを同時にレンダリングできるようになります
is limited
制限されています
so how do you find effective content and present it
では、効果的なコンテンツを見つけて提示するにはどうすればよいでしょうか
this is very complicated
これはとても複雑です
there is another
もう一つの...がある
A very important one like our Pingliang
私たちの平涼のような非常に重要なもの
There is a kind of Pingliang called Situation Pingliang
平涼には状況平涼という種類があります。
What is Pingjing Pingliang? For example, we
平京平梁とは何ですか?
us
私たち
go to the entrance
入り口に行く
right
右
Don't you need a driver's license to drive?
運転するのに運転免許証は必要ないのですか？
driver's license you need to go to the entrance
運転免許証は入り口に行く必要があります
The entrance test is that you actually go into the situation and then take the test.
入学テストは実際にその状況に入ってテストを受けるものです。
You can judge after that
それから判断すればいいよ
This is called a good situation
これを良い状況といいます
In this peaceful environment
この穏やかな環境の中で
It is impossible to do it in a real educational environment.
実際の教育現場ではそれは不可能です。
So how do you get through this mobility vehicle
では、このモビリティビークルをどのように使用するのでしょうか
Achieving a goal of peace of mind
安心という目標の達成
so hard to do
とてもやりにくい
I actually don't have many standard answers for this part
実はこの部分については標準的な答えがあまりありません
I'm all constantly
私はみんないつも
I'll go and find out
行って調べてみます
I do a find out what exactly is
正確に何なのか調べてみます
what should be done better
何をもっと良くすべきか
Then there is another one
それからもう一つあります
Then how do I evaluate his learning effect?
では、彼の学習効果をどのように評価すればよいのでしょうか?
And he applied the whole process
そして彼はプロセス全体を適用しました
did you record it for me
私のために録音してくれましたか
Also the design of your entire event
イベント全体のデザインも
Learning in action throughout
全体を通じて実践的な学習
Design of the whole event
イベント全体のデザイン
The result of this design
この設計の結果
How do you evaluate whether he is good or not?
彼が良いかどうかをどう評価しますか?
i evaluate him
私は彼を評価します
he is right or wrong
彼は正しいか間違っているか
Then assess whether he is motivated to learn?
次に、彼が学習意欲があるかどうかを評価しますか?
right
右
a situation like this
このような状況
Don't think that sometimes mobile vehicle design is too fun
時々モバイル車両のデザインが楽しすぎるとは思わないでください
Strong motivation to learn
学習に対する強いモチベーション
but his learning motivation
しかし、彼の学習動機は
Where are you so strong? So strong because this loading technique is fun
どこがそんなに強いの? この装填テクニックが楽しいから強い
not your content is fun
あなたのコンテンツは面白くありません
So your final learning effect is not good
つまり、最終的な学習効果は良くありません
Therefore, being motivated to learn does not mean that there is a learning effect.
したがって、学習意欲があるからといって学習効果があるとは限りません。
Because your loading skills are so interesting
君のローディングスキルがとても面白いから
like gamified learning
ゲーム化された学習のような
right?
右？
Gamified learning is done well
ゲーム化された学習はうまく行われています
is really hard to do
本当に難しいです
You have both the function of the game and the effect of learning
ゲームの機能と学習効果の両方を兼ね備えています
really hard to do
本当に難しい
I've only seen one so far and probably nothing else.
まだ一匹しか見たことがなく、おそらく他には何も見ていない。
We all play games now, right? It’s fun, isn’t it?
今みんなゲームしてますよね、楽しいですよね？
But there is no learning effect
でも学習効果は無い
Therefore, learning is a kind of learning software design based on games.
したがって、学習はゲームに基づいて設計された学習ソフトウェアの一種です。
is hard to design
設計するのが難しい
Well, but if your design is successful
まあ、でも、あなたのデザインが成功したら
that would be a big deal
それは大変なことになるだろう
We know that there are many kinds of nurturing
育成にはさまざまな種類があることを私たちは知っています
It is difficult to develop a
を開発するのは難しい
We make it a value development
私たちはそれを価値開発にします
develop an attitude
態度を養う
is hard
は難しい
Everyone has different values
人それぞれ価値観が違います
So you're going to change a person's politics
それであなたは人の政治を変えるつもりですか
a political or religious belief
政治的または宗教的信念
is hard
は難しい
Sometimes education is not enough
教育だけでは不十分な場合もある
so it's hard for you to change it
だからそれを変えるのは難しい
I remember
私は覚えています
a few years ago, about ten years ago, ten years ago
数年前、約10年前、10年前
there was a survey
調査がありました
Investigation seems to be idol pair
捜査はアイドルコンビらしい
A Survey of Human Idols
人間アイドルに関する調査
As a result, the politicians came to the back
その結果、政治家が後押しするようになった
Who is the number one, do you know?
誰が一番なのか、知っていますか？
Cao Cao
曹操
Why is Cao Cao ranked first?
なぜ曹操が1位なのでしょうか？
Because at that time there was a game software
当時ゲームソフトがあったので
About the game software of Romance of the Three Kingdoms
三国志のゲームソフトについて
very smart
とても賢い
and he's cosplaying
そして彼はコスプレをしています
you can play cao cao
曹操をプレイできます
Play Liu Bei and play anything
劉備をプレイして何でもプレイ
As a result, he changed one of his ideas
その結果、彼は自分の考えを一つ変えました
change his attitude
彼の態度を変える
so it's hard
だから大変だよ
Being able to design this kind of game can make money
この種のゲームをデザインできればお金を稼げる
another change of mind
別の心変わり
is also very difficult
それもとても難しいです
To change a concept through which place
どのような場所を通じて概念を変えるのか
cooperative game
協力ゲーム
So I work with a group of people through cooperation
だから私は協力して人々のグループと仕事をしています
to solve a certain difficulty of the game
ゲームの特定の難しさを解決するために
that might change your values
それはあなたの価値観を変えるかもしれません
So the interaction between people is very important
ですから人と人との交流はとても大切です
you teach honestly
あなたは正直に教えます
to try to change his political stance
彼の政治的立場を変えようとする
try to change his religion
彼の宗教を変えようとする
it's actually hard
実際は難しいです
But if a body
しかし、もし身体ならば、
It is possible to change after a long time
時間が経てば変わる可能性もある
so this place
それでこの場所
So this part of the evaluation method is difficult to do
したがって、評価方法のこの部分は実行が困難です
Now our general education assessment method
さて、私たちの一般教育評価方法
probably several
おそらくいくつかの
Generally, there are quantitative methods and value analysis
一般的には、定量的な手法と価値分析があります。
Quantitative method, we use experimental group, control group, etc.
定量的方法では、実験群、対照群などを使用します。
then compare
それから比較してください
The value analysis we have to do
私たちがしなければならない価値分析
take a picture of its information
その情報の写真を撮る
We'll do tape analysis after the filming
撮影後にテープ分析を行います
tape analysis
テープ分析
See how his behavior changes
彼の行動がどのように変化するかを確認してください
this can be done
これはできる
Now there is old science
今は古い科学があります
an application to education
教育への応用
also doing
もやっている
But the question is now what
しかし、問題は今、何をするかです
This action learning is
このアクションラーニングは、
I don't know where the students go
生徒たちがどこへ行くのか分からない
Like we used to do action learning in museums
かつて博物館でアクションラーニングをしていたように
that's hard work
それは大変な仕事だ
First
初め
Because they are all elementary school students
みんな小学生だから
So we're afraid he'll drop our tablet on the ground
だから私たちは彼がタブレットを地面に落とすのではないかと心配しています
We can't blame him for falling into the ground and ruining it.
私たちは彼が地面に落ちて台無しにしたことを責めることはできません。
So we specially designed a bag to drop here
そこで、ここに落とし込むためのバッグを特別にデザインしました
Let him stay like this even if he falls
転んでも首に残る
fall over there
そこに落ちます
but we have to collect him
でも彼を集めなければならない
collect his information
彼の情報を収集する
Is that right? Collect his information and write that we sometimes don’t know each other.
そうですか? 彼の情報を集めて、私たちがお互いのことを知らないこともあると書きましょう。
So I had to make another hat, this is student No. 1, student No. 2
それで、別の帽子を作らなければなりませんでした、これは生徒 1 号と生徒 2 号です
make lots of hats for them to put on their heads
彼らの頭にかぶせる帽子をたくさん作る
Then we start designing
それからデザインを始めます
design
設計
But sometimes they talk
でも時々彼らは話します
I can't hear the discussion sometimes.
時々議論が聞こえないことがあります。
so again
それでまた
Are you going to use that hidden microphone again?
またその隠しマイクを使うつもりですか？
Because I can't let them know that there is a microphone
マイクがあることを知らせられないから
they started not to speak
彼らは話さなくなり始めた
hidden microphone
隠しマイク
But I want to see the expression on his face
でも彼の表情が見たい
So I had to add one to the mobile vehicle
そこで、移動車両に 1 つ追加する必要がありました
CAMERA
カメラ
I design
私がデザインします
so complicated
とても複雑
It was hard work, it was hard work to do that experiment.
その実験をするのは大変です、大変です
spend a lot of money
たくさんのお金を費やします
But this way of evaluating
しかし、この評価の仕方
indeed in action
実際に活動中
ubiquitous learning inside
内部のユビキタス学習
is a complicated part
複雑な部分です
It is also necessary to conduct a discussion
話し合いを行うことも必要です
In addition, there is a digital content application guide
また、デジタルコンテンツ申請ガイドもございます。
The first online learning resource
最初の e ラーニング リソース
This learning resource is very important
この学習リソースは非常に重要です
For example, the current simulation software
たとえば、現在のシミュレーション ソフトウェアでは、
We put a lot of abstract things
抽象的なものをたくさん入れています
Design through simulation software
シミュレーションソフトによる設計
simulate on the computer
コンピューター上でシミュレーションする
electric second wave
電気の第二波
And the learning simulation has an important part
そして学習シミュレーションには重要な部分があります
The simulation of the game is different
ゲームのシミュレーションは異なります
Like many gamification software nowadays, it is simulation
最近の多くのゲーミフィケーション ソフトウェアと同様、これはシミュレーションです
you become a mayor
あなたは市長になります
or you are a government
それともあなたは政府ですか
then how do you build a city
じゃあどうやって街を作るのか
So that software is complicated
そのソフトウェアは複雑なので、
The software we trade with is not that complicated
私たちが取引するソフトウェアはそれほど複雑ではありません
Why? Because I just talked about the concept of scaffolding
なぜかというと、足場の概念についてお話ししたばかりだからです。
That is to say I can start from the simple pattern
つまり、簡単なパターンから始めることができます
tell you the result
結果を教えてください
Then slowly add the complex
次に、ゆっくりと複合体を追加します
So we don't start by putting the most complex situation in
したがって、最初から最も複雑な状況を組み込む代わりに、
Instead, gradually add complexity
代わりに、徐々に複雑さを加えていきます
So the simulation is a simplified simulation of
したがって、シミュレーションは次の単純化されたシミュレーションです。
Sometimes it works better
場合によってはそのほうがうまくいくこともある
If game software it's full emulation
ゲームソフトなら完全エミュレーション
sometimes it doesn't work
時々うまくいかないこともあります
So there's just too much to do in one design
つまり、1 つのデザインでできることが多すぎるのです
There is too much of a learning karma
学習カルマが多すぎる
Now Silverside itself is your learning software
Silverside 自体が学習ソフトウェアになります
put your resources on
リソースを投入する
Is there any change in the part of your presentation?
プレゼンテーションの部分に変更はありますか？
How to manage this place effectively
この場所を効果的に管理する方法
Then how to do an effective presentation
では、効果的なプレゼンテーションを行うにはどうすればよいか
In addition, in the wireless network
さらに、ワイヤレスとネットワーク
In the case of a mobile carrier
携帯キャリアの場合
Can these learning contents be cross-platform?
これらの学習コンテンツはクロスプラットフォームで使用できますか?
Something like this has to be dealt with
このようなことは対処しなければなりません
Then this one is and the other one is information technology
それから、これはそうです、そしてもう一つは情報技術です。
Integrate into teaching and learning
教育と学習に統合する
this part
この部分
we have less time
時間が少ない
But it's an important place
でも大事な場所です
Well, Taiwan has implemented it for more than ten years.
そうですね、台湾は10年以上前からそれを実施しています。
So teachers have many ways to use
教師にはさまざまな使い方があります
Intellectual Technology In fact, all tools can do
知的テクノロジー 実際、すべてのツールでできること
all tools can do
すべてのツールでできること
For example, you can teach simple statistics with Xare
たとえば、Xare を使用して簡単な統計を教えることができます。
teachers can use
教師が使用できる
I just remember a teacher who was very good at them
とても上手だった先生を思い出します
Teaching for him to teach statistics
彼に統計を教えてもらうための教育
teach students statistics and then
生徒に統計を教えてから
Then he started to design
それから彼はデザインを始めました
he's the first he wants to get motivated
彼が一番最初にやる気を出したいのは彼だ
How does he arouse motivation? He puts a lot of information
彼はどうやってモチベーションをかき立てているのですか? 彼はたくさんの情報を載せます。
Messy and show on PowerPoint
乱雑でPowerPointで表示
Then ask the students, what is the relationship between these numbers?
次に、これらの数字の間にはどのような関係があるのか​​を生徒たちに尋ねます。
That student must not understand
あの生徒は理解できないはずだ
I don't know what's the matter
何が起こったのか分かりません
He said that I will change the mode for you
彼は、私があなたのためにモデルを変更すると言いました
and then after clicking
そしてクリックした後
After pressing it, the numbers will start to run slowly
押すと数字がゆっくりと動き始めます
Run into a statistical result
統計結果に遭遇する
Then you say what's the relationship
じゃあどういう関係なのかと言うと
written achievement is very clear
書かれた成果は非常に明確です
he just for motivation
彼はただモチベーションのためだけに
For students interested in statistics
統計に興味のある学生向け
He does such a treatment
彼はそのような治療をします
There is another one who doesn't know there are children here
ここに子供たちがいることを知らない人がもう一人います
I don't know if I should talk
話すべきか分かりません
Then don't take me as the principal of the Normal University
それなら私を師範大学の校長だと思わないでください
it caused me to talk about the professor
それがきっかけで教授のことを話した
Because the president of the normal university sometimes
普通の大学の学長も時々いるので
more responsibilities
さらなる責任
This is actually the problem
実はこれが問題なのです
In fact, there are teachers who teach
実際に教えてくれる先生もいます
don't we have sex education
私たちは性教育をしていないのでしょうか
right
右
How about sex education
性教育はどうですか
And he's talking about animal sex
そして彼は動物のセックスについて話しています
I don't know why there is such a class
なぜそのようなクラスがあるのか​​わかりません
It's really the teacher who teaches like this
本当にこんなことを教えてくれる先生なんですね
how does he do you know
彼はどうやって知っていますか
He was just at that time
彼はちょうどその時だった
Discovery
発見
He has a company for his videos
彼は自分のビデオのための会社を持っています
Buy the rights to Discovery
Discovery の権利を購入する
That copyright can be picked up segment by segment
著作権はセグメントごとに取得できること
It's not the whole film, it's picked up piece by piece
それは映画全体ではなく、部分的にピックアップされています
then put it on the web
それからそれをウェブに載せます
Then he put the sexual behavior of animals in Discover
それから彼は動物の性行動をDiscoverに載せました。
Then hand it over to sketch in class
その後、クラスでスケッチするためにそれを渡します
Let Sketchbook understand this essay question
スケッチブックにこのエッセイの質問を理解させましょう
Then you say there is no video, how can we teach it?
では、ビデオがないと言いますが、どうやって教えればよいのでしょうか？
There is no way to actually operate it.
実際に操作する方法はありません。
Right, it’s hard, right, it’s really hard
そうだよ、大変だよ、そうだよ、本当に大変だよ
But there is such a course
でもそういうコースもあるんですね
But I saw that he was very natural after teaching.
しかし、私は彼が教えた後とても自然であることに気づきました。
very natural
とても自然な
Therefore, in fact, many media
そのため、実際に多くのメディアが
Always felt a need to have a lot to teach
たくさんのことを教えなければならないと常に感じていた
but very embarrassing
でもとても恥ずかしい
But after going through the media, it became normal
でもメディアを通してそれが普通になった
become normal, something like this
普通になる、こんな感じ
So the teacher will also do this
じゃあ先生もこうするよ
so they can find many
彼らはたくさん見つけることができるように
I also saw a teacher
先生にも会いました
I've asked many people what to do
たくさんの人にどうしたらいいのか聞いてみました
There was an earthquake at that time, right?
その時、地震がありましたよね？
He's going to teach that tremor
彼はその震えを教えるつもりだ
How strong is the vibration of your earthquake?
地震の揺れの強さはどのくらいですか?
he did it for the first time
彼は初めてそれをした
How about the earthquake in the first episode, it's moving on the screen
第一話の地震はどうですか、画面上で動いています。
How did you move in the first episode? How did you move in the second episode? Move even more
1話ではどう動いた? 2話ではどう動いた? もっと動いて
By the end of the episode, the screen broke
エピソードが終わる頃には画面が割れた
If you want to move until it breaks, you have to simulate it completely
壊れるまで動かしたいなら徹底的にシミュレーションする必要がある
It must be simulated completely. There is also such a method
完全にシミュレーションする必要がありますが、そういう方法もあります
So this is very interesting, and in fact our domestic
これは非常に興味深いことであり、実際、私たちの国内では
Teacher Zhuang Xiaoyi's ability in this area is usually pretty good
Zhuang Xiaoyi 先生のこの分野の能力は通常かなり優れています。
Our teacher is quite serious
私たちの先生はとても真面目です
just because it's a pity
ただ残念だから
Most of this is done by elementary school teachers.
そのほとんどは小学校の教師によって行われます。
Because he doesn't have the entrance exam pressure, he doesn't have the entrance exam
彼には入学試験のプレッシャーがないので、入学試験はありません。
I also saw an example
私も例を見ました
a music teacher
音楽の先生
because he was going to teach that
彼はそれを教えるつもりだったから
It seems that the elementary school plays the flute or the tendons
小学校では笛か腱を吹いているようです
But every time I play the flute
でもフルートを吹くたびに
Because the piano teacher needs an accompaniment, right?
ピアノの先生には伴奏が必要だからですよね？
Only the body of the shoe can play the flute
靴の本体だけでフルートを演奏できます
But he said that every time we were playing the accompaniment
でも彼は、私たちが伴奏を演奏するたびにこう言いました。
I really do not know
私は本当に知らない
How about the students blowing
生徒たちが吹いているのはどうですか？
He really doesn't know because he's playing the accompaniment
彼は伴奏を弾いているので本当に知りません
But then it was very simple, he just used a computer
でもそれはとても単純で、ただコンピューターを使っただけだった
Then he asked the computer to do the accompaniment
それから彼はコンピュータに伴奏をするように頼みました
So the computer is playing the accompaniment and he listens to it one by one
コンピューターが伴奏を再生し、彼はそれを一つ一つ聞きます
So the computer becomes his assistant
それでコンピュータは彼のアシスタントになります
My assistant went to play the accompaniment and he listened to them one by one
アシスタントが伴奏をしに行って、一つ一つ聞いてくれました。
How about blowing the bottom? It's a music teacher's job.
お尻を吹くのはどうですか? それは音楽教師の仕事です。
So in other words, there are actually a lot of creative ways
言い換えれば、実際には創造的な方法がたくさんあるということです
It actually exists in our teaching environment
それは私たちの教育環境に実際に存在します
It's also quite a conscious approach.
これもかなり意識的なアプローチです。
I used to teach calligraphy. Our Dean Wang Hu is a calligrapher.
私は書道を教えていましたが、学部長のワン・フーは書道家です。
I heard that calligraphy must be the first to draw red
書道は赤を描くのが先だそうです
step by step
一歩ずつ
That teacher, he is very good
あの先生、とてもいい人ですよ
He wrote it himself first and then asked someone to take a picture of it
彼は最初に自分で書いて、それから誰かに写真を撮ってもらった
After shooting, in that step
撮影後のその段階で
he put it
彼はそれを置きました
play it out
遊んでみる
he uses media play
他用media play
Then media play can repeat
その後、メディア再生を繰り返すことができます
So the same comparison he kept
それで彼は同じ比較を続けました
My fart let the students watch
私のオナラが生徒たちに見られるようになった
I let the students see how he wrote
私は生徒たちに彼がどのように書いたかを見させた
I keep showing him
私は彼に見せ続けています
If you were to teach yourself how
もし自分にその方法を教えたとしたら
i remember when i was young
若い頃のことを思い出します
The teacher taught us to write with a brush, right?
先生は私たちに毛筆で書くことを教えましたよね？
a soul pen and draw again
ソウルペンでまた描く
that can't be done at all
それはまったくできません
So there are also teachers who do it specially.
ですから、特別にやっている先生もいます。
So this is an auxiliary tool and it is also very effective.
したがって、これは補助ツールであり、非常に効果的です。
There is also a kind of university
大学のようなものもあります
Especially now that the general education courses in universities
特に今は大学の一般教養科目
Because Taiwan really does not have a kind of university
台湾には本当に大学というものが存在しないので、
It is a truly neutral university
本当に中立的な大学です
I often say that it is a transfer to a neutral university
中立大学への編入だとよく言います。
For example, National Taiwan University does not have music and fine arts
例えば、国立台湾大学には音楽や美術がありません。
Normal University has no business
師範大学にはビジネスがない
But your general education, especially the current future development
しかし、あなたの一般的な教育、特に現在の将来の発展
General education courses are increasingly important
一般教育コースの重要性がますます高まっている
We often say that we will have cultural and creative industries in the future
私たちはよく、将来は文化的でクリエイティブな産業が生まれると言います。
right
右
But cultural and creative industries
しかし、文化・クリエイティブ産業
I often tell the professors in our music department
私は音楽学部の教授たちによく言います。
I said every time I go to a concert
コンサートに行くたびに言ってました
Looking forward to gas is to understand the concert
コンサートを理解してガスを楽しみにしています
I said, can you help us find a solution?
私は、解決策を見つけるのを手伝ってくれませんか、と言いました。
People like me who don't understand music are willing to spend money
私のような音楽を理解できない人は喜んでお金を使います
Come and listen to your symphony industry
交響楽団の音楽を聴きに来てください
Come and listen to your pipe business, right?
あなたのパイプビジネスを聞きに来てください?
You have to find a way to create a market
市場を作る方法を見つけなければなりません
Your market will expand
あなたの市場は拡大します
Also you have to cultivate an existing culture
また、既存の文化を育てなければなりません
creative industries, the industry
クリエイティブ産業、業界
you must have a market then you must have a market
あなたには市場が必要です、そしてあなたには市場が必要です
So you have to be in the colleague transaction
したがって、同僚トランザクションに参加する必要があります
Let's improve our cultural literacy, right?
文化的リテラシーを向上させましょう。
In the future, the things we design will look like LV
将来、私たちがデザインするものはLVのようになります
Everyone at least we expand
少なくとも私たちは拡大します
So we have to pay mainland cultural literacy
だから私たちは本土の文化的リテラシーを支払わなければならない
Why because it's important after we put it together
理由は、まとめた後が重要だからです。
Its market is huge, right? We don't want to wait for a professional
その市場は巨大ですよね？専門家を待ちたくないのです
But we develop our colleagues so that it knows it's literate
しかし、私たちは同僚が読み書きできるように教育します。
it has musicality
音楽性がある
So I often talk to some of our music department teachers and folklore
それで私はよく音楽科の先生たちと民間伝承について話します。
Because the Music Folklore of Normal University
師範大学の音楽フォークロアだから
Every time it is the first industry in the country
国内初の産業となるたびに
Then every time our other students
それから、他の生徒が来るたびに、
going to his class next to him
彼の隣のクラスに行く
or take his class
または彼の授業を受ける
they all season
彼らはオールシーズン
I said why is it like this?
どうしてこうなったの？と私は言いました。
I said you can't open a music app
音楽アプリを開けないって言ったよね
drive more
もっと運転する
let these students
この生徒たちにさせてください
Everyone knows how to appreciate music
誰もが音楽の鑑賞方法を知っています
Isn't your market bigger?
あなたの市場はもっと大きくないですか？
right
右
Are you still afraid that your major will be expected by others?
自分の専攻が他の人から期待されるのではないかとまだ恐れていますか?
impossible things
不可能なこと
Because you are in the last four years
あなたは過去4年間にいるから
They hurry up for a year or two
彼らは1年か2年を急いでいます
so the euphoria amplifies it
だから多幸感がそれを増幅させる
the market will be bigger
市場はもっと大きくなるだろう
As a result I think we are now
その結果、今があると思います
The one watching the art exhibition
美術展を見ている人
not those buyers to see
見るべき購入者ではない
Then just know how to draw
あとは描き方を知るだけです
As far as people in the art world look at each other
アート界の人々がお互いを見る限り
look at each other
お互いを見て
then the music is all
それなら音楽がすべてだ
Those who know music should listen
音楽に詳しい人は聞いてみてください
Listen to Jay Chou for everything else
その他のことはジェイ・チョウの話を聞いてください
this feels bad
これは気分が悪い
all bad
全部悪い
Then this should be an exhibition
だったらこれは展示会になるはずだ
do it complementary
補完的にやります
Here is a very important thing to say
ここで非常に重要なことを言います
Teaching and learning theories throughout digital learning
デジタル学習全体にわたる指導と学習の理論
and a development of strategy and evaluation
戦略の策定と評価
I just talked about the issue of education
先ほど教育の問題についてお話しました
It's been a hundred years
百年経ちました
But it creates this problem
しかし、それがこの問題を引き起こします
It is all in the process of interaction between people
それはすべて人と人との相互作用の過程にあります
developed it
それを開発した
But once information technology comes in
しかし、ひとたび情報技術が登場すると、
some of it affects education
一部は教育に影響を与える
Whether it's the sequelae
後遺症なのか
or a change in its learning strategy
または学習戦略の変更
will have an impact
影響を与えるだろう
On this side, we need to conduct a new discussion
こちら側では新たな議論が必要だ
So this is the difficulty and here
ここが難しいところであり、ここが
So why start putting a lot of
では、なぜたくさんのものを入れ始めるのでしょうか？
brain science wait to put it in
脳科学はそれを入れるのを待ってください
just to understand
ただ理解するために
With the intervention of such technology
そういったテクノロジーの介在により、
Is there any other theory we want to develop
他に開発したい理論はありますか
This is also a difficult part
ここも難しい部分です
How to do it from a cognitive point of view
認知的な観点からそれを行う方法
How to understand how its brain changes
脳がどのように変化するかを理解する方法
There is a process, how does the process work
プロセスがありますが、そのプロセスはどのように機能しますか
So this place is worth exploring
したがって、この場所は探索する価値があります
What about his sequelae, what sequelae do you have?
彼の後遺症はどうですか、どんな後遺症がありますか？
In fact, I often tell many people
実際、私は多くの人によく言いますが、
In fact, computers are really fascinating
実はコンピューターって本当に面白いんです
Whether you are a mobile phone or a tablet computer
携帯電話でもタブレットコンピュータでも
Or a personal computer, both are fascinating
それともパーソナルコンピュータ、どちらも魅力的です
But because he's charming, it's easy to get lost
でも魅力的だから迷いやすい
Because he has too many sequelae that will cause
あまりにも多くの後遺症を抱えているため、
But if you don't deal with it well, you will really get lost
でも、うまく対処しないと本当に道に迷ってしまいます
The impact might last a lifetime
その影響は一生続くかもしれない
You can do your own experiments
自分自身の実験を行うことができます
say you are above your office
あなたはオフィスの上にいると言う
next to you if you use the computer a lot
コンピューターをよく使うならあなたの隣に
You use a computer next to you, so you study here
隣にパソコンがあるのでここで勉強します
I assure you that you will not concentrate on reading
読書に集中できないことは保証します
Because you run into your computer every 15 minutes
15分ごとにコンピューターにアクセスするため
Check if there is an email coming in
メールが来ているか確認する
See if anyone wants to chat with you on Facebook
Facebook であなたとチャットしたい人がいないか確認してください
Is that right?
そうですか？
You're mentally retarded, right?
あなたは精神薄弱者ですよね？
That's too much insurance
それは保険が多すぎる
but if you do well
でもうまくやれば
I teach parents a trick
親にコツを教えます
This is very important
これはとても重要です
my wife did it
私の妻がやった
because my son
私の息子だから
When I was from elementary school to middle school
小学生から中学生の頃
that summer vacation
あの夏休み
One day during that summer vacation, he said
そんな夏休みのある日、彼はこう言った。
He wants to chat with his classmates
彼はクラスメートとおしゃべりしたいと思っています
This is not bad
これは悪くない
Since I just graduated, I want to chat with my classmates
卒業したばかりなのでクラスメイトとおしゃべりしたい
We thought you were a good kid
私たちはあなたが良い子だと思っていました
Why
なぜ
Because before full of classmates
前はクラスメイトでいっぱいだから
it's time why don't you go out
時間だよ、出かけてみない？
I can't figure it out
分かりません
It's time to come, why don't you go out and chat
そろそろ時間だ、外に出ておしゃべりしませんか
still at home
まだ家にいる
Later I found out that their so-called chatting is online chatting
後で知ったのですが、彼らのいわゆるチャットとはオンラインチャットのことです。
I said is it that serious?
私は言いました、それはそんなに深刻ですか？
Doesn't your classmate live next door to ours?
あなたのクラスメートは私たちの家の隣に住んでいませんか？
also chat online
オンラインでチャットすることもできます
He chats online every day
彼は毎日オンラインでチャットしています
strangeness
奇妙さ
Then we chatted for a while
それからしばらくおしゃべりしました
about two weeks later
約2週間後
I am very impressed
すごく感動しました
A girl from Hualing High School wrote a letter
華陵高校の女子生徒が手紙を書きました
really write a letter
本当に手紙を書きます
Will being a parent be stressful?
親になるとストレスが溜まるのでしょうか？
A girl who just graduated from elementary school and a girl from Hualien High School wrote to him
小学校を卒業したばかりの女の子と花蓮高校の女の子が手紙を書いた。
I'm scared to death
死ぬほど怖いです
But that person is small
でもあの人は小さい
So use half of it to read his letter
だから半分は彼の手紙を読むために使ってください
I always let us think about it halfway and I see his letter
いつも中途半端に考えさせてもらって、彼の手紙を見るのですが、
Fortunately, there is no problem
幸いなことに問題はありません
I am more at ease
もっと安心です
but how many parents do things
しかし、どれだけの親が何かをするか
because of this
このため
so i won't let you go online
だから私はあなたをオンラインにさせません
blocked you
あなたをブロックしました
right
右
I want to block more seriously sometimes
たまにはもっと本気でブロックしたい
because where will he go
なぜなら彼はどこへ行くのでしょう
he went to internet cafe
彼はインターネットカフェに行きました
Internet cafes were very popular back then, right?
当時はネットカフェが大人気でしたよね。
that's not more serious
それはもっと深刻なことではありません
then what should we do
じゃあどうすればいいのか
There are several strategies to do
やるべき戦略はいくつかあります
First
初め
if the child was young
もし子供が小さかったら
You put all your computers in a shared place
すべてのコンピュータを共有の場所に置く
in the study
この研究で
If he surfs the Internet for a long time, you walk around next to him
彼が長時間ネットサーフィンをしていると、あなたは彼の隣を歩き回る
Make him uncomfortable online
オンラインで彼を不快にさせる
my first
私の最初の
The second is because Yahoo didn’t need money back then.
2つ目は、当時Yahooにはお金が必要なかったからです。
so my wife because my wife is a fast typer
それで妻は、私の妻はタイピングが速いので、
He went online to apply for an account
彼はオンラインでアカウントを申請しました
then he does role play
それから彼はロールプレイをします
He chatted with my son online
彼は私の息子とオンラインでチャットしました
Then half a year is his
それから半年は彼のものです
classmate's
クラスメイトの
your classmate
あなたのクラスメート
that's good that's really useful
それはいいですね、本当に役に立ちます
When he passed the exam, he went online to talk to him about it.
彼は試験に合格したとき、それについて話すためにオンラインにアクセスしました。
My mom said that's what he was going to say
私の母は、それが彼が言おうとしていたことだと言った
My mother said because we want to take the exam
試験を受けたいから母が言った
So we have to work hard, what?
だから私たちは頑張らなければなりません、何ですか？
He didn't know until college
彼は大学まで知らなかった
which girl is his mother
彼の母親はどの女の子ですか
hehe
ふふふ
So it’s really good if you do well on the Internet, right?
インターネットでうまくやれば、それは本当に良いことですよね？
Existing tutoring function
既存の個別指導機能
It depends on how you use it
それは使い方次第です
So everyone thinks that Xie Computer is also good
だからみんなはXie Computerも良いと思っています
It's good to type faster
タイピングが早くなると良いですね
He always has this instrument, right?
彼はいつもこの楽器を持っていますよね？
You can go tutor your own children
自分の子供に家庭教師をしに行くこともできます
similar to this
これに似たもの
But there are so many unknowns
でも未知の部分が多すぎて
we really need to develop
私たちは本当に開発する必要があります
There are too many theories that are not yet known
まだ知られていない理論が多すぎる
of course i don't know yet
もちろんまだ分かりません
So I say that this field has an advantage that is to say
つまり、この分野には利点があると言えます。
can almost redo the problem of education
教育問題はほぼやり直すことができる
platform change
プラットフォームの変更
I usually change
普通に変えるんだよ
So this is full
それでこれはいっぱいです
In addition, the roles of teachers and agreements have changed
さらに、教師の役割と協定も変化しました
This is the most impressive
これが一番印象的です
I am a graduate student
私は大学院生です
that graduate student
あの大学院生
He once I was looking for a software
彼はかつて私がソフトウェアを探していたとき、
I can't find it
見つからない
He said it's okay, teacher, I'll give it to you in a few days
彼は「大丈夫です、先生、数日以内に渡します」と言いました。
He really gave it to me in a few days
彼は本当に数日以内にそれを私にくれました
I wonder why he is so powerful
なぜ彼はそんなに強いのか不思議です
why so powerful
なぜそんなに強力なのか
he can give me something right away
彼はすぐに私に何かをくれるでしょう
he doesn't speak
彼は話さない
Later it was hard
後は大変でした
Then his information ability is much better than mine
それなら彼の情報能力は私よりはるかに優れています
Later he
その後彼は
just graduated
卒業したばかり
His cooperation told me teacher you know
彼の協力は先生が知っていると私に言いました
He is the stationmaster of the underground website outside
彼は地下ウェブサイトの外の駅長です
So I actually have a student
それで、実際に生徒がいます
underground webmaster
地下ウェブマスター
You can get me various software
色々なソフトを入手してもらえる
i feel weird
変な気がする
what does this mean
これは何を意味するのでしょうか
If we use this angle of information
この角度からの情報を使うと
I can't keep it up
それを維持することはできません
Because his IT skills are much better than mine
彼のITスキルは私よりもはるかに優れているため
So I say a kind of teacher
だから私は一種の教師と言っています
The role of university teachers needs to be changed
大学教員の役割を変える必要がある
What you want to teach him may not be direct knowledge
あなたが彼に教えたいことは、直接的な知識ではないかもしれません
It's the meta knowledge
それはメタ知識です
may become like this
こうなるかもしれない
one change one big change
一つの変化が一つの大きな変化
there is another one
もう一つあります
He used to have an Altros at Central University
彼はかつて中央大学でアルトロスを持っていました
Then you can start classes on Altros
その後、Altros で授業を開始できます
Then he later transferred Altros to Chunghwa Telecom
その後、Altros を中華電信に譲渡しました。
Turns out there is a very hot teacher
とても熱い先生がいることが判明しました
That Besker I'm talking about is Chen Shiyuan
私が話しているベスカーとは、チェン・シーユアンのことです
very popular
非常に人気のある
Then I found out that the teacher
それで先生が気づいたのですが、
Is a student of the Central China Normal University
中国中部師範大学の学生です
do you know wes
ウェスを知っていますか
So on the Internet you will feel that
したがって、インターネット上では次のように感じるでしょう。
You think he's great, maybe he's a teacher
あなたは彼を素晴らしいと思う、もしかしたら彼は教師かもしれない
it could be me but what
それは私かもしれませんが、何ですか
he can wes
彼はできます
But in real environment
しかし実際の環境では
he is your student
彼はあなたの生徒です
So this role is a big change
したがって、この役割は大きな変化です
You know a lot about the roles of teachers and students
あなたは教師と生徒の役割についてよく知っています
In particular, the role of the teacher needs to change
特に教師の役割は変わる必要がある
The role of the teacher what you are going to teach him
教師の役割 何を教えるのか
may not be transfer of knowledge
知識の伝達ではないかもしれない
but another aspect
しかし別の側面
my change
私の変化
what about the second one
2番目はどうですか
The way students learn also changes
生徒の学び方も変わる
my way of learning
私の学習方法
The teacher may later become a facilitator
教師は後にファシリテーターになる可能性があります
He's also a no-talker
彼は口も利けない人でもある
Come up with a topic and guide
トピックとガイドを考え出す
guide
ガイド
one of our practices
私たちの実践の一つ
However, the perspective of students has also changed.
しかし、学生の視点も変わりました。
Now there is a kind of interactive communication
今では一種のインタラクティブなコミュニケーションが行われています
That is to say, we have always believed that
つまり、私たちは常に次のように信じてきました。
If students can ask questions
生徒が質問できる場合
The student's understanding of knowledge is very high
学生の知識に対する理解力は非常に高い
so often what happens
頻繁に何が起こるか
meeting
ミーティング
The student poses a question for another student to answer
学生が他の学生に答えてもらうために質問をする
can you understand me
私が言うことを分かりますか
I do this often
これをよくやります
The teacher-student perspective has changed
教師と生徒の視点が変わりました
But our traditional education is still a big problem
しかし、私たちの伝統的な教育には依然として大きな問題があります
You want our primary school teacher
あなたは私たちの小学校の先生が欲しいのです
I think our elementary school teachers are really hardworking
小学校の先生方は本当に勤勉だと思います
salary is not high
給料は高くない
a lot of working hours
労働時間が長い
Why
なぜ
Change homework every time
毎回宿題を変える
raw knowledge
生智部
Do you have any impression
何か感想はありますか
If a word is wrong in the Ministry of Health and Intelligence
保健情報省の言葉が間違っている場合
I have to write 30 times when I go home, right?
家に帰ったら30回は書かないといけないですよね？
The job of the teacher is to pick out the shortcomings of the students
教師の仕事は生徒の欠点を見つけることです
what's wrong where's wrong
何が間違っているのか、どこが間違っているのか
Then the job is like this
それでは仕事はこんな感じです
multiple choice
複数の選択肢
Clear choice
明確な選択
Then that answer is C
そうすると答えはCです
Choose A for sketching, right?
スケッチする場合はAを選択しますよね？
Then sketch must write CCC 3 times next to A
次に、スケッチは A の隣に CCC を 3 回書き込む必要があります。
Is it this way
こうですか
Isn't it strange that we teach you to speak
私たちが教えるのはおかしくないですか？
Then the calculation problem was wrong, right?
じゃあ計算問題が間違ってたんですよね？
Then go back to timeout
その後、タイムアウトに戻ります
Write that process 10 times
その処理を10回書く
How can this education improve
この教育をどのように改善できるか
Because SASIS is still wrong
SASISはまだ間違っているから
We sketch the same word can be wrong
私たちは同じ言葉をスケッチしますが、間違っている可能性があります
Maybe I'm still wrong until I'm 20
もしかしたら20歳になるまでは間違っているかもしれない
why is this
どうしてこれなの
because you never gave him a chance to find fault
あなたは彼にあら探しの機会を与えなかったから
So I often tell the teacher
そこで私はよく先生に言います。
The first one, your salary is not high
1つ目は給料が高くないこと
Because I once gave a speech at an elementary school
小学校で演説したことがあるから
i was very angry
私はとても怒っていました
I'm speaking and I speak so well
私は話しています、そしてとても上手に話します
The bottom is changing homework
一番下は宿題の変更です
you will be angry
あなたは怒るでしょう
I'm changing my homework the next day, right?
次の日に宿題を変えるんですよね？
ah you can blame them
ああ、彼らを責めてもいいよ
Thinking about it later, it's really pathetic
後から考えると本当に情けないです
because we all asked him to
私たち全員が彼にそう頼んだから
Look at the teacher in Anqing Class
安慶教室の先生を見てください
Anqing class teacher
安慶市のクラスの先生
Is it his job only to do
することだけが彼の仕事なのか
Just change homework
宿題を変えるだけ
So let our students have a habit
だから生徒たちに習慣を身につけてもらいましょう
very bad habit
とても悪い習慣
we only have one thing to do
私たちがやるべきことは1つだけです
but didn't do a thing well
でも何もうまくできなかった
Many of our graduate students are like this
大学院生にはこんな人が多いです
Right? That's why I never help students.
そうですか?だから私は決して生徒を助けません。
I helped a student revise a paper once
私は一度学生の論文の添削を手伝いました
I'm almost editing his composition
彼の作曲をほぼ編集しているところです
I'm so angry that I'm yours after all
結局のところ私はあなたのものなのでとても怒っています
Information teacher or your Chinese teacher?
情報の先生ですか、それとも中国語の先生ですか？
Every time I have to help him change his composition
彼の構成を変えるのを手伝う必要があるたびに
That word, I found a typo
その言葉、タイプミスを見つけました
I'm always like this
私はいつもこんな感じです
that's not right
それは違います
So it should be reversed
だから逆転すればいいのに
In fact, our parents have to be patient.
実際、私たちの親は忍耐強くなければなりません。
And teachers have to communicate with parents
そして教師は保護者とコミュニケーションを取る必要があります
For example, find that typo
たとえば、そのタイプミスを見つけてください
why don't you look for it like this
こうやって探してみませんか
You just ask the students to find typos
生徒にタイプミスを見つけるように指示するだけです
homework for students to go back on their own
生徒が自分で戻るための宿題
Just start by saying that there are two mistakes on this page
このページには 2 つの間違いがあると言って始めてください。
go back and find it, right?
戻って見つけてくださいね？
Students go back and find it by themselves.
生徒たちは戻って自分たちで見つけます。
The young age on that page, will you be able to find it the first time you look for it?
そのページの若い頃、初めて探したら見つかるでしょうか？
Are you sure you won't find it?
きっと見つからないんですか？
Because they never had that belief
なぜなら彼らにはそのような信念がなかったからです
so he won't find
だから彼は見つからないでしょう
what to do if you can't find it
見つからなかったらどうするか
It doesn't matter if you come back. It's always okay.
戻ってきても大丈夫、いつでも大丈夫です。
It doesn't matter if you can't find it on this page
このページで見つからなくても大丈夫です
Then there is a typo in Shang Han.
それから、『商漢』にタイプミスがあります。
You just switch to zoom out, right?
ズームアウトに切り替えるだけですよね？
Go back and look for it, he will look for it from inside Shang Han
戻って探してください、彼はシャンハンの中から探します
What if you still can't find it?
それでも見つからない場合はどうすればよいですか?
Then there is a typo in one line, right?
それから、一行にタイプミスがありますよね？
Is there a typo in the three words?
3 つの単語にタイプミスはありますか?
one time you'll find
一度見つけてください
But you also develop an opportunity for him to self-diagnose
しかし、あなたは彼が自己診断する機会も作ります。
right, you said that math
そう、あなたは数学のことを言いました
That counting error in how many students we have is a miscalculation
生徒数の数え間違いは計算違いです
But what will they know later that he miscalculated
しかし、彼が計算を誤っていたことを後で彼らは何を知ることになるでしょうか
If you let them find the wrong reason every time
毎回間違った理由を探させたら
They make a typo every time because I miscalculated
私が計算を間違えたので、彼らは毎回タイプミスをします
I tell you after the current events he will
現在の出来事の後に彼はそうするでしょう
Will there be any more miscalculations?
これ以上の誤算はあるだろうか？
because he'll know he's miscalculated every time he's wrong
なぜなら、彼は間違うたびに自分の計算が間違っていることに気づくからです。
right like this
まさにこのように
The same is true for composition changes, because every time students
構成を変更する場合も同様です。
It’s very hard for the teacher to correct them. Of course, you can help him correct a few articles.
教師がそれらを修正するのは非常に困難ですが、いくつかの記事を修正するのを手伝うことはもちろんできます。
Because you have to comment, sometimes you can exchange and change the composition
コメントしないといけないので、たまにやりとりしたり構成を変えたりすることもできます
Let me tell you that we humans have a common problem
私たち人間には共通の問題があるということを教えてください
I can’t even find my own fault, so I’m very accurate in finding someone else’s fault
私は自分の欠点を見つけることさえできないので、他の人にそれをやってもらうのが非常に正確です。
Right? After you exchange and change
そうでしょ?交換して交換してから
Let me tell you he picks faults very well
言っておきますが、彼は欠点をとても上手に見つけます
Right, it's ok after changing it a few times
そうですね、何度か変えたら大丈夫です
This human really needs to be cultivated but almost none of us have
この人間は本当に育成する必要があるが、それを持っている人はほとんどいない
How can I do this kind of training with a computer?
コンピュータを使ってこのようなトレーニングを行うにはどうすればよいでしょうか?
right
右
The computer itself is to create an environment
コンピュータ自体が環境を構築するもの
But this environment is always in use
ただし、この環境は常に使用されています
It is an environment that helps students learn
学生の学びをサポートする環境です
Rather than expecting students to learn
生徒に学ぶことを期待するのではなく、
So one of this part
つまり、この部分の 1 つが
because how did i jump here
だってどうやってここにジャンプしたんだろう
I was just here
私はちょうどここにいました
Therefore, the roles of teachers and students are sometimes
したがって、教師と生徒の役割は、場合によっては
Adjust it. When I am a teacher, I often
私が教師をしているとき、私はよく、
Then the salary is not very high, each salary increase is only 3%
その場合、給与はそれほど高くはなく、昇給はわずか 3% です。
as little as he does that doesn't have to work
彼がするのと同じくらい、それは働く必要はない
Too responsible teachers sometimes create irresponsible students
責任感が強すぎる教師は無責任な生徒を生み出すことがある
This, the evaluation of the effectiveness method
これが、有効性の評価方法です。
This, this at present, before Ye Lai
これ、これ、今、イェライの前
bright marriage salary, or straight marriage salary
明るい結婚の給料、またはストレートな結婚の給料
Now it's mass blending together to do
今、それを行うために大量のブレンドが行われています
And then put brain science into it
そこに脳科学を導入する
So this kind of marriage salary model is more and more, more and more development
したがって、この種の結婚給与モデルはますます、ますます開発されています
even through videotape
ビデオテープを通してでも
After you shoot the videotape, then
ビデオテープを撮影したら、
Then describe its learning status
次に、その学習状況を説明します
Which learning state would you jump from this learning state to?
この学習状態からどの学習状態にジャンプしますか?
Then jump from this learning state to which angle, and then evaluate
次に、この学習状態からどの角度にジャンプして評価しますか
Is there a significant difference from this state to this state?
この状態とこの状態で大きな違いはありますか?
I use statistics, so I will put the statistics
統計を使っているので統計を載せておきます
Integrate with that straight marriage salary
そのストレートな結婚給与と統合する
Liang and Zhi will integrate it together, so this is a more and more scientific approach
Liang と Zhi はそれを統合する予定なので、これはますます科学的なアプローチになります。
Okay, so this is the part about information literacy
さて、ここからは情報リテラシーについての部分です
This has probably been mentioned just now, the first digit gap
これは先ほども触れたかと思いますが、最初の桁のギャップです。
This number is far behind Taiwan
この数字は台湾に大きく及ばない
So far so good, but there are some problems
ここまでは順調ですが、いくつか問題があります
In recent years, the situation of digital gap has indeed been
近年、デジタルギャップの状況はまさに深刻化しています。
That is to say, your symbiosis in the north
つまり、北におけるあなたの共生
Is it similar to the South's symbiosis information capability?
それは南の共生の情報能力に似ているでしょうか？
Now it's not a digital gap
今はデジタルギャップではない
Now we in Taiwan don't seem to be
今、台湾にいる私たちはそうではないようです
Like Yinyin gap, math gap
陰音ギャップ、数学ギャップのように
It seems that there are all kinds of gaps
色々なギャップがあるようです
Yes, it's getting worse
はい、悪化しています
The gap in that part is getting worse
その部分のギャップがひどくなっている
this is
これは
It has indeed improved a lot in recent years.
確かにその点は近年大きく改善されました。
Of course there is one more
もちろんもう一つあります
How do you detect this gap?
このギャップをどのように検出しますか?
how do you define
どのように定義しますか
The so-called digital gap
いわゆるデジタルギャップ
Digital gap
デジタルギャップ
how do you detect it
どうやって検出しますか
And then react very quickly
そして、非常に迅速に反応します
On the contrary, this mechanism is not easy to do.
逆に言えば、この仕組みは簡単ではありません。
How do you define what is called drop
ドロップと呼ばれるものをどう定義しますか
Then in this gap
そうするとこの隙間に
A print that can be accessed through the Internet
インターネット経由でアクセスできるプリント
and react anytime
そしていつでも反応する
How much has the situation of its gap changed?
そのギャップの状況はどれくらい変わったのでしょうか？
So this should be dealt with by the government
だからこれは政府が対応すべきだ
Additional Internet Literacy Section
追加のインターネット リテラシー セクション
It has probably been said just now
たぶん今も言われたと思う
Now Internet literacy does not mean that you understand the principles of the Internet
現在、インターネット リテラシーはインターネットの原則を理解していることを意味するものではありません
For example, 70% of your network has a network protocol
たとえば、ネットワークの 70% にネットワーク プロトコルが存在するとします。
That kind of agreement is not about that
そういう合意はそういうことではない
That's a professional doing it
それをやっているのはプロです
But where is the quality of a non-professional person?
しかし、専門家ではない人の資質はどこにあるのでしょうか？
So are we going to redefine it?
では、再定義してみましょうか？
And now different technology comes in
そして今、さまざまなテクノロジーが入ってきています
Various technologies come in
様々な技術が入ってくる
Is that a form of your problem solving?
それはあなたの問題解決の形ですか？
will also change
も変わります
like this
このような
this is
これは
That's the hardest thing to do right now
それが今一番難しいことだよ
I'm still working on a very interesting topic
私はまだ非常に興味深いテーマに取り組んでいます
We call it presence
私たちはそれをプレゼンスと呼びます
presence
臨場感
For example we do
たとえば、私たちはそうします
Now everyone is very present, right?
今はみんなとても存在感がありますよね？
because we can talk to each other
お互いに話せるから
face to face
面と向かって
But when on the Internet
しかし、インターネット上では
your teacher may be in taipei
あなたの先生は台北にいるかもしれません
Then your business students may be all over the world
そうすれば、あなたのビジネスの学生は世界中にいるかもしれません
His sense of presence is gone
彼の存在感が消えてしまった
right
右
What about the sense of presence?
存在感はどうでしょうか？
Then how do you improve the sense of presence?
では、どうすれば臨場感を高めることができるのでしょうか？
I'm in trouble now
今困っています
what is presence
存在感とは何ですか
how do you define presence
存在感をどのように定義しますか
So a group of teachers are studying this
それで、教師のグループがこれを研究しています
specializing in how
どのように特化するか
Improving the sense of presence in the Internet age
インターネット時代の臨場感向上
Now I know like geoprotocol
今私は地理プロトコルのようなものを知っています
sense of place
場所の感覚
I just recently developed a sense of place
最近、場所の感覚が発達したばかりです
For example, if I go to Tamsui
例えば淡水に行くと
after freshwater
淡水の後
what methods can i use to improve my sense of place in freshwater
淡水での場所の感覚を改善するにはどのような方法を使用できますか
As far as I agree with Tamsui
淡水さんの意見に同意する限り
then what about me
それなら私はどうですか
It has a definition out
定義がありません
I am very abstract
私はとても抽象的です
start slowly materializing it
ゆっくりと具体化し始める
slowly quantify it
ゆっくりと数値化してみる
So this whole process
つまり、このプロセス全体が
The history I use is also currently in
私が使用している履歴も現在あります
A discussion like this
このような議論
So when I used to be on the Internet
それで、私がインターネットにいた頃
Problems that would not exist in the non-Internet era
非インターネット時代には存在しなかった問題
However, in the era of Internet in mainland China, there will be
しかし、中国本土でもインターネットの時代には、
The topic of this study arises
この研究のテーマが生まれる
How can we discuss the sense of presence in education like before?
教育における臨場感を以前のように議論するにはどうすればよいでしょうか？
No, because it's all natural
いや、それは当然のことだから
want to be together
一緒にいたい
But in the Internet age
しかしインターネット時代では
Presence becomes very important
存在感がとても重要になる
We want to improve our sense of presence
存在感を高めたい
right
右
that...that...
それ...それ...
Well...motivation is also important
そうですね…モチベーションも大事です
for example
例えば
how do i... how do i increase your motivation to study
どうすれば...どうすれば勉強のモチベーションを高めることができますか
The learning motivation is only
学習動機はあくまで
What is the motivation for learning for the first time?
初めて学ぶ動機は何ですか？
Still need magnetism for learning motivation
学習意欲にはやはり磁力が必要
right
右
How to improve it
改善方法
i through the internet
私はインターネットを通じて
how can i raise it
どうすれば上げられますか
Because your individual study is very lonely
個人の勉強はとても孤独だから
because in the classroom
なぜなら教室にいるから
you have companions
あなたには仲間がいます
but when online
しかしオンラインのときは
you are learning alone
あなたは一人で学んでいます
you are doing it yourself
あなたは自分でやっているのです
that's what you're doing
それがあなたがやっていることです
How do you improve his learning motivation
どうすれば彼の学習意欲を高めることができますか
And this motive needs a magnet
そしてこの動機には磁石が必要です
right
右
so something like this one
それで、このようなもの
this question
この質問
to discuss
話し合う
a part of him
彼の一部
Of course, there are generally two motivations for learning.
もちろん、学習には一般的に 2 つの動機があります。
class motivation
授業のモチベーション
One is extrinsic motivation
一つは外発的動機づけ
a class in an external
外部のクラス
that generally speaking
一般的に言えば
small child
小さな子供
Usually you need extrinsic motivation.
通常、外発的動機付けが必要です。
So we also encourage the power system
したがって、私たちは電力システムも奨励します
must reconsider
必須要再考
If there is progress, then you will give it to him
進展があれば彼にあげるよ
give him a little gift
彼にちょっとした贈り物をする
This is outside winter
こちらは冬以外です
We grown-ups too, why are you investing in stocks?
私たち大人も、なぜ株式投資をしているのでしょうか？
Because there is winter outside, because you will make money
外には冬があるから、お金が儲かるから
Right, but when you often lose money
そうですね、でもお金を失うことが多いときは
So what to do, you have to study how to make money
じゃあどうするか、お金の稼ぎ方を勉強する必要がある
so you might look into that
それでそれを調べてみるといいかもしれません
What technical analysis of what stock?
どの銘柄のどのようなテクニカル分析ですか?
But you may study to a certain stage
ただし、一定の段階までは勉強することもできます
you think he's funny
彼は面白いと思いますか
Right? Not only can he help you make money, but he
そう?彼はあなたがお金を稼ぐのを手伝ってくれるだけでなく、
there is his smell
彼の匂いがそこにある
Then change from external winter to internal winter
そして、外の冬から内なる冬に変わります。
Because you think it's interesting and you're willing to take over again
面白いと思ってまた引き受ける気があるから。
So we are often motivated from the outside
そのため、私たちは外部から刺激を受けることがよくあります。
then switch to the inner
それからインナーに切り替えます
So the initial motivation
それで最初の動機は
computerized a motive
動機をコンピューター化した
computer games or computer
コンピューターゲームとかコンピューターとか
computer washing part
パソコン洗浄部分
just arouse your motivation first
まずはモチベーションを高めてください
To arouse you through the external winter
外の冬を乗り越えるためにあなたを目覚めさせます
But slowly it will return to the inner winter
でもゆっくりと内なる冬に戻っていきます
otherwise he won't last
そうでなければ彼は長続きしないだろう
won't last like this whole research journey
この研究の旅全体のようには続かないでしょう
Another very important
もう一つ非常に重要な
Now
現在
in the internet age
インターネット時代に
A very important one is the sequelae of the Internet
非常に重要なのはインターネットの後遺症です
My sequelae are really big
私の後遺症は本当に大きいです
What is the sequelae?
後遺症とは何ですか？
There's really something we don't know yet
本当にまだ知らないことがあるんです
Then we still have to explore
それならまだ探索する必要があります
Now I only know that there are many people sitting in Internet cafes
今私が知っているのは、インターネットカフェにたくさんの人が座っているということだけです
After sitting for a long time, the result is a stroke
長時間座ると脳卒中になる
I'm all sequelae
私はすべて後遺症です
Then I just said that when you were next to a computer
それから私はあなたがコンピューターの隣にいるときに言いました
you sit on this side he will interfere with you
あなたはこちら側に座ります、彼はあなたの邪魔をするでしょう
right
右
I have a lot of sequelae like this
こういう後遺症がたくさんある
Is there any age difference
年齢差はありますか
For example, say you have reached a certain grade
たとえば、ある学年に到達したとします。
after age
年齢を重ねてから
These side effects are gone
これらの副作用はなくなりました
disappear without form
ただ消える
But you are below high school
でも君は高校生以下だよ
you like on facebook
フェイスブックで「いいね！」
Like many adults don't like to go to Facebook these days
多くの大人と同じように、最近は Facebook が好きではありません
right
右
because feel
感じるから
There's no point in chatting with him online.
彼とオンラインでチャットしても意味がありません。
But kids love it
でも子供たちは大好きです
right
右
So is there an effect of age?
では、年齢の影響はあるのでしょうか？
I have a discussion topic like this
こんなディスカッショントピックがあります
I'm worth it
私にはそれだけの価値がある
to study
勉強する
I specifically bring this up as
私はこれを具体的に次のように取り上げます
Because of
なぜなら
So we want to be able to
だから私たちはできるようになりたいのです
And this can indeed improve
そしてこれは実際に改善することができます
motive for action
行動機
Increase ability to act
行動力を高める
So how should you design
では、どのようにデザインすればよいのでしょうか
But gamification software
しかし、ゲーミフィケーション ソフトウェア
If saving the game itself
ゲーム自体を保存する場合
it also has side effects
副作用もあります
So this is a very difficult design
これは非常に難しいデザインです
so we call it
それで私たちはそれを呼びます
serious game
真剣勝負
serious is a very serious game
シリアスは非常に真剣なゲームです
then you have a solution
それなら解決策があります
This is a contradiction, the game can still be very serious
これは矛盾しています、ゲームは依然として非常に深刻である可能性があります
But the application of education is to be like this
しかし教育の応用とはこうあるべきだ
So this is a very complex
これは非常に複雑です
a part, a development of a very complex part
部品、非常に複雑な部品の開発
Of course this is too
もちろんこれもです
worth exploring, because in fact
実際に、調査する価値があります。
it exists
それが存在します
There is also this phenomenon
こんな現象もあります
So how do we put the game part
では、ゲーム部分をどのように配置するか
import it into learning
それを学習に取り入れます
more normal use
より通常の使用
So there's a lot of the same
だから同じものがたくさんあるんだよ
its content design , its theory
コンテンツデザイン、理論
and evaluation of its strategy
とその戦略の評価
even its man-machine interface
マンマシンインターフェースさえも
This tool needs to be discussed and developed
このツールについては議論して開発する必要がある
It's a really difficult part
本当に難しい部分です
Let's take a look at the part that is currently under development.
現在開発中の部分を見てみましょう。
i need to do it again
もう一度やらなければなりません
What are the possible future scenarios?
考えられる将来のシナリオは何ですか?
my first
私の最初の
your future classroom
あなたの未来の教室
future school etc.
未来の学校など
future learning style
これからの学習スタイル
even future teachers
将来の教師であっても
I recently talked to our
最近私たちと話しました
Our physical education teacher said
私たちの体育の先生は言いました
I said we have so many players
我々にはたくさんの選手がいると言いました
right
右
So many players often compete outside
非常に多くのプレーヤーが屋外で頻繁に競争します
Then how do we provide a good teaching model
では、どのようにして優れた教育モデルを提供すればよいのでしょうか
instead of saying
言う代わりに
Only for class or what kind of use
授業だけとかどんな用途に使うか
Are there different ways of teaching
いろいろな教え方があるのでしょうか
Let these players learn more
これらのプレイヤーにもっと学んでもらいましょう
then his
それから彼の
his grades are better
彼の成績はもっと良いです
And he's more employable in the future
そして彼は将来的により雇用されやすい
Instead of saying that I have three marriages
私は3回結婚していると言う代わりに
how many hours are you coming
何時間くらい来ますか
But he is often not there
でも彼はそこにいないことが多い
what to do
何をすべきか
so something like this
だからこのようなもの
There seems to be an experimental one abroad in the UK
海外ではイギリスで実験的なものが行われているようです
one
一個
For example, he said that when you go to a certain department
例えば、ある部署に行くとこう言いました。
Then he set up to say
それから彼はこう言い始めた
Okay, you've only had to solve 20 problems for four years
わかりました、4 年間で 20 個の問題を解くだけで済みます
After you solve all the problems, you will graduate
すべての問題を解決したら卒業です
But every question he asks is to cross fields
しかし、彼が尋ねるすべての質問は分野を横断するものです
You have to read a lot of books to understand
理解するにはたくさんの本を読まなければなりません
problem-oriented planetary model
問題指向型惑星モデル
I also have such a practice
私もそんな練習してます
From now on, there will be more media and more tools
これからはメディアもツールも増えるだろう
The change of the form of your evil image
あなたの邪悪なイメージの形の変化
Now there is another terrible
今、また恐ろしいことが起きた
I don't know when
いつなのかわからない
Also, the development of digital TV in Taiwan is relatively slow
また、台湾におけるデジタル TV の発展は比較的遅いです。
After that, the digitalized machine price environment will be slanted
その後、デジタル化された機械の価格環境は傾く
because digital tv
デジタルテレビだから
A digital TV is a computer from a certain point of view
デジタルテレビもある観点からはコンピュータです
So many of your interactive teaching desks can be placed on it
非常に多くのインタラクティブな教育机を設置できます
so i hope he doesn't arrive so early
だから彼がそんなに早く到着しないことを願っています
Because I prefer to enjoy life
人生を楽しみたいから
I'm sitting in the living room and I still have to study with you, right?
私はリビングルームに座っていますが、まだあなたと一緒に勉強しなければなりませんね？
I might as well go to a acting show, right?
演技ショーに行ったほうがいいですよね？
But this is weird
でもこれは変だよ
But there may be such a problem in the future
でも将来的にはそういう問題が起きるかもしれない
So will this have side effects?
それで、これには副作用がありますか？
you digital tv
あなたはデジタルテレビです
Then you have interactivity again
そして、再びインタラクティブ性が得られます
Digital teaching materials come again
デジタル教材再び登場
digital teaching material
デジタル教材
right
右
And he can interact with you
そして彼はあなたと対話することができます
and integrated with the phone system
電話システムと統合されています
right
右
see half broken
半分壊れているのを見てください
There is another call in
また電話がかかってきました
tell you not to sleep
眠らないように言う
what to do
何をすべきか
right
右
so troublesome
とても面倒です
The aftermath of this
この余波
very scary
とても怖い
right
右
So Taiwan's digital TV didn't come so early
つまり、台湾のデジタルテレビはそれほど早く登場しなかったのです
otherwise it will be miserable
そうしないと悲惨なことになります
Will this affect
これは影響しますか
Will
意思
From the point of view of the assisting community
支援コミュニティの観点から
inevitable problem
避けられない問題
we need to discuss
話し合う必要があります
hopefully we'll find out
できれば分かると思います
normal learning style
通常の学習スタイル
right
右
reduce its sequelae
後遺症を軽減する
So a situation like this
それでこのような状況
It will be a very troublesome thing in the future
将来的には大変なことになります
there is another
もう一つの...がある
electronic learning machine
電子学習機
or digital toys
またはデジタルおもちゃ
Another smart online learning tool
もう一つのスマートなオンライン学習ツール
Join the iPad
加入iPad
EPad
EPad
This is an information feed
これは情報フィードです
if you design
あなたがデザインするなら
he really is a message
彼は本当にメッセージだ
It's like I'm talking about your iPad in the future
まるで未来のiPadについて話しているようだ
As soon as the relevant information is posted here, it will come out.
ここで関連情報が取得され次第、すぐに出てきます。
He will deal with you
彼はあなたに対処してくれるでしょう
it's all possible
それはすべて可能です
Because this technology also exists
こんな技術もあるんだから
right
右
That Pedro you must face now
あなたが今直面しなければならないペドロ
we did something recently
私たちは最近何かをしました
all our supervisors all
私たちの監督者全員
All can't bury the iPad
全部都埋不iPad
so they are happy
それで彼らは幸せです
You see, the principal is good.
なるほど、校長先生はいいですね。
Give us one iPad per person
iPadを1人1台プレゼント
Then I gave him a reason and said
それから私は彼に理由を言ってこう言いました
no way
とんでもない
Because the principal is presbyopic
校長が老眼なので
So I bought an iPad after all to amplify it
それで、結局それを増幅させるためにiPadを購入しました
Otherwise, can't you see it every time you look at the paper?
そうでなければ、紙を見るたびにそれが見えないでしょうか？
they thought this
彼らはこう思った
Actually where is my male model
実際のところ、私の男性モデルはどこにいますか
Because someone has an iPad since then
それ以来誰かがiPadを持っているので
I don't spend paper anymore
もう紙を使わない
All paper, all endless
すべて紙、すべてエンドレス
Only then did they know that my purpose is to promote endless
その時になって初めて、彼らは私の目的が無限のプロモーションであることを知りました。
So while there's an iPad on it that can zoom in
ズームインできるiPadがある間
so happy
とても幸せ
But it works well
でもそれはうまくいきます
I think we are always learning now
私たちは今、常に学んでいると思います
After giving one, everyone is looking forward to it
贈った後はみんな楽しみにしています
As a result, the first time I came to a meeting, there was no paper
その結果、初めて会議に来たときは紙がありませんでした
Without paper, he started looking at the computer
紙がないので、彼はコンピュータを見始めた
look at the screen and so on
画面などを見てください
The meeting was also good
会見もよかったです
so this changes
それでこれは変わります
this is a tool
これはツールです
Therefore, in the future, this electronic protocol tool
したがって、将来的には、この電子プロトコルツールは
will really come more
本当にもっと来るでしょう
But what will the teacher do in the future if there are sequelae?
しかし、もし後遺症が出たら先生は今後どうするのでしょうか？
I'm thinking everyone gets an iPad
みんなiPadを買うと思うよ
right
右
Then every protocol member is busy in class
その後、プロトコルの各メンバーは授業で忙しいです
don't even look at the teacher
先生の方も見ないで
I have a feeling after endless transformation
果てしなく変化した後に感じることがある
I am the chairman and no one wants to see me
私は会長だけど誰も私に会いたがらない
no one wants to see me
誰も私に会いたくない
Everyone is looking at his iPad and not at me
誰もが私ではなく自分のiPadを見ています
This is also a very troublesome thing in the future
これも今後非常に困ることです
don't know how to explain the problem
問題をどう説明したらいいのかわからない
later you see
後でわかります
In the future, if each symbiotic can keep one step
これからも、それぞれの共生が一歩を踏み出せたら
He just looks at his iPad
彼はただiPadを見ているだけです
Look at his tutorial tools
彼のチュートリアルツールを見てください
I see his tutorial tool
彼のチュートリアルツールを見ました
Then the teacher interacts with the students
その後、教師が生徒と対話します
How to link this mechanism again
この機構を再度接続する方法
how to connect again
再度接続する方法
So this needs to be dealt with
したがって、これに対処する必要があります
one of the satellites
衛星の一つ
an online learning tool
オンライン学習ツール
like that quiz
あのクイズみたいに
right
右
Our school has developed several testing systems
私たちの学校はいくつかのテストシステムを開発しました
also quite intelligent
非常に知的でもあります
In terms of language, we have developed
言語に関しては、私たちが開発したのは、
For example, a few indicators and a few parameters
たとえば、いくつかのインジケーターといくつかのパラメータ
This parameter can be used to judge the readability of your article
このパラメータは記事の読みやすさを判断するために使用できます。
i have readability
私には可読性があります
Then we have done a set of rewriting
次に、一連の書き換えを行いました
that is we have a new book center
それは新しいブックセンターがあります
Specially responsible for junior high school locomotives
中学校機関車を特別担当
original design purpose
本来の設計目的
See if you can expect the teacher to correct the composition
教師が作文を修正してくれると期待できるかどうかを確認する
Because it doesn't mean that the composition is graded
作文に等級があるわけではないので
That design is really good
あのデザインも本当に良いですね
and we have evaluated
そして私たちは評価しました
change with real people
現実の人々と変化する
change with computer
パソコンで変える
how relevant is it
それはどの程度関連性がありますか
Its related machine is almost the same
関連マシンはほぼ同じ
That is to say, you use a computer to change
つまり、コンピュータを使って変更します。
follow the employer to change
雇用主に従って変わる
Actually not much difference
実際には大差ない
In the end we dare not launch
結局、私たちはあえて立ち上げることはしませんでした
Why dare not launch
なぜあえて起動しないのか
Because no matter what you say, the parents won't believe it
何を言っても親は信じないから
that
それか
Parents don't believe it
親は信じない
The computer can be shocked
コンピューターがショックを受ける可能性があります
The idea is the same, right?
考え方は同じですよね？
How could his parents believe that the composition was modified by a computer?
彼の両親はどうしてコンピューターが構図を変えたと信じたのでしょうか?
It's the same as people change
人が変わるのと同じです
Even if there is no so-called difference in our research
たとえ我々の研究にいわゆる差異がなかったとしても
But we just dare not use that to change
しかし、私たちはそれを変えるために敢えてそれを使用しません
or use people to change
あるいは人を使って変える
Then use someone to change it
それから誰かを使ってそれを変えてください
But sometimes people are wiser
でも時には人間の方が賢いこともある
Like our current new car center, the remodeling is very powerful
現在の新車センター同様、改造は非常に強力です
So you have to believe it's fair
だからそれが公平だと信じなければならない
Why
なぜ
I'll tell you a secret
秘密を教えます
All the composition teachers corrected all the essays on the computer
作文の先生全員がコンピューター上ですべての作文を添削します
So all your sketches and essays
あなたのスケッチやエッセイはすべて
All will be scanned into the computer
すべてがスキャンされてコンピューターに取り込まれます
So you look at the computers in the classroom
それで教室のコンピューターを見てみると
All composition correction teachers sat on it and corrected
作文添削の先生全員がその上に座って添削していただきました
Then when changing, we will hide some compositions
次に、変更するときにいくつかの構成を非表示にします
Already know which set of compositions
どの構成セットかはすでにわかっています
we have already classified
私たちはすでに分類しました
For example, this composition has been divided into three episodes
たとえば、この構成は 3 つのエピソードに分かれています
Then he will write this composition
それから彼はこの作文を書くでしょう
plug it into one of our teachers
それを私たちの教師に接続してください
The teacher didn't know that this side thought it was our tears
先生は知らない、こちら側が私たちの涙だと思っていること
It's us hiding inside, not the composition of the co-existence
共存の構成ではなく、中に隠れているのは私たちです
It's us, just...so that teacher will change
私たちだよ、ただ…あの先生が変わるように
Then if he changed it, he gave it a score of six
その後、それを変更すると、スコアは 6 になりました
what does that mean?
どういう意味ですか？
The standard should be three points.
目安は3点です。
Then how do you give six points?
ではどうやって6点を与えるのでしょうか？
So naturally a teacher would go to him
だから当然、先生は彼のところに行くだろう
that teacher will get him
あの先生が彼を捕まえるだろう
Go to a counselor for counseling
カウンセラーに相談に行く
Just ask him what's your problem?
彼に何が問題なのか聞いてみてください。
Then you start doing counseling
それからカウンセリングを始めます
So as long as you are found, it means you have a problem
つまり、見つかったということは、問題があるということです
So we use something like this
したがって、このようなものを使用します
So there is a counseling mechanism put in
そこでカウンセリングの仕組みが導入されています
Of course, education and training must be done before changing the composition
もちろん、構成を変更する前に教育と訓練を行う必要があります
tell everything
すべてを話してください
But in education and training, we still have to be afraid of many human factors.
しかし、教育や訓練においては、依然として多くの人的要因を恐れる必要があります。
So we will insert some composition into it
それで、それにいくつかのコンポジションを挿入します
Then ask him to correct the composition
それから彼に構図を修正してもらいます
After asking him to change it, if the deviation is too large
変更してもらった後、乖離が大きすぎる場合
we start tutoring
私たちは家庭教師を始めます
So something like this, this even the test has to come to us
だから、このようなこと、これはテストさえも私たちに来なければなりません
use our trick
私たちのトリックを使ってください
He also needs to change the exam, right?
彼は試験も変える必要があるよね？
this is called
これは呼ばれます
So we all have faith in our counselors
だから私たちは皆、カウンセラーを信頼しています
Everything can only be changed after belief
すべては信じた後にのみ変えられる
The smart eLearning process
スマートな e ラーニング プロセス
A four-star teaching
四つ星の教え
I can follow your ability
私はあなたの能力に従うことができます
To judge your ability and give you different teaching materials
あなたの能力を判断し、異なる教材を提供する
I give you different teaching materials
いろいろな教材をあげます
Now the four-star test is very important
今、四つ星テストは非常に重要です
It is to give you different tests according to your ability
それはあなたの能力に応じてさまざまなテストを与えることです
So the quiz questions are different for each of you
クイズの質問は人それぞれ異なります
Give points based on your quiz questions
クイズの質問に基づいてポイントを付与します
So he has such a practice
それで彼はそのような習慣を持っています
that this
これは
this can never be done
これは決してできません
because this is too much
これは多すぎるので
too much worth doing
やる価値がありすぎる
Another one is that
もう一つはそれです
this should be next
これは次のはずです
The whole small screen learning content
小さな画面全体の学習コンテンツ
when the screen was small
画面が小さかった頃
picture
像
if you are a tablet
タブレットの場合
still slightly larger
まだ少し大きい
If your phone is smaller
携帯電話が小さい場合
right
右
A design of the whole learning content
学習コンテンツ全体のデザイン
There are also four-star digital learning content
4 つ星のデジタル学習コンテンツもあります
it will be the kind of talent
それは一種の才能だろう
Learning Content
学習内容
That gives you different content for judging your ability
それにより、自分の能力を判断するためのさまざまなコンテンツが提供されます
This is a very complicated part of me
これは私の中で非常に複雑な部分です
There are also agreements other than knowledge learning
知識学習以外の協定もあります
Like this I have been encouraging teachers to do
このように私は先生たちにこうするように勧めてきました
For example, how do you design a learning tool
たとえば、学習ツールをどのように設計しますか?
To develop students' communication skills
生徒のコミュニケーション能力を伸ばすために
how do you design a learning tool
学習ツールをどのように設計しますか
To develop students' ability to be business owners
学生のビジネスオーナーとしての能力を開発する
It's not about knowledge
知識の問題ではない
So how do you design tools to develop students' reasoning skills?
では、生徒の推論スキルを伸ばすツールをどのように設計すればよいでしょうか?
A practice like this
こんな練習も
This place is really worth developing
この場所は本当に開発する価値があります
and it's not easy to do
そしてそれは簡単ではありません
OK good
いいよ
Then I'm probably very simple in the end
そうすると、結局のところ私はとても単純なのかもしれない
make a conclusion
結論を出す
there are several parts
いくつかの部分があります
The first environment where handrails no longer learn
手すりが学習しなくなった最初の環境
more and more international attention
ますます国際的な注目が高まる
Plus the future camp end
さらに将来のキャンプ終了
This will definitely change our education a lot.
これは間違いなく私たちの教育を大きく変えるでしょう。
Especially after the 12-year state religion came in
特に12年間の国教が導入されてからは
time stretched
時間延長
After a stretch
ストレッチの後
it will change a lot
大きく変わるだろう
so
それで
Now the balance of that camp
さて、そのキャンプのバランスは
Platform usage is simply too high
プラットフォームの使用率が高すぎる
And now many students are very good at taking a small software on the silver terminal as falling
そして今、多くの学生は、銀色の端末上の小さなソフトウェアが落ちているものとして捉えるのが非常に上手です。
Then learn directly on the screen
画面上で直接学習できます
and even while
そしてその間も
So maybe in the future we will be very similar to Japan
ですから、将来的には日本とよく似たものになるかもしれません。
For example, if you go to Japan to do his MRT
たとえば、MRT に乗るために日本に行くとします。
You will see a lot of Japanese people playing with their mobile phones over there, right?
あそこでは携帯電話で遊んでいる日本人をたくさん見かけますよね？
We also hope that one day we in Taiwan will also look at mobile phones
また、いつか台湾の私たちも携帯電話に目を向けることを願っています。
But looking at the learning class cage
でも学習教室の檻を見てみると
In this way, our competitiveness is higher than his
このようにして、私たちの競争力は彼よりも高いです
He watched maybe a game and we watched learning cages
彼はおそらく試合を見て、私たちはケージの学習を見ました
maybe there will be
もしかしたらあるかもしれない
unit becomes small
単位が小さくなる
For example, your study time becomes shorter
例えば勉強時間が短くなった
there are a lot of shortening
短縮が多いです
But the aftereffects of the place I just talked about
でもさっき話した場所の後遺症
Knowledge will be very spilled
知識が非常に流出します
The second high-quality learning environment
第二の質の高い学習環境
Not limited to online learning
オンライン学習に限らず
for dust learning
粉塵学習用
in the school system
学校制度の中で
transmission of knowledge
知識の伝達
The transmission effect between people is better
人々の間での伝達効果がより優れています
through computer
コンピューターを通して
It doesn't deliver that well
それはあまりうまくいきません
Then how do you teach the entity
では、エンティティにどのように教えますか
Integrate it with online teaching
オンライン教育と統合する
put it together
一緒に置く
one like this
このようなもの
For example, in your laboratory you do experiments
たとえば、研究室で実験をするとします。
do experiments
実験を行います
on the internet
インターネット上で
Networked labs have their advantages
ネットワーク化されたラボには利点がある
what's the advantage
何が利点ですか
because it is simulated
シミュレートされているので
simulate a laboratory
実験室をシミュレートする
Simulating a lab has one benefit
ラボのシミュレーションには 1 つの利点があります
what it can do
それは何ができるのか
from failure
失敗から
write in error
誤って書く
Trial and error is not written in doing
試行錯誤はやることには書かれていない
We put a lot of emphasis on writing in Chinese
私たちは中国語で書くことに重点を置いています
But what?
でも何？
If it is on the Internet, it can be wrongly written
ネット上だと間違って書かれる可能性もある
you keep on trial and error
あなたは試行錯誤を続ける
I try and make mistakes because it's safe
安全だから試したり失敗したりする
it can be safe from mistakes
間違いを避けることができます
i remember
私は覚えています
I bought one of those before
そのうちの一つを以前購入しました
That Microsoft designed a Flightshake
マイクロソフトがフライトシェイクを設計したこと
Just simulate waving, right?
手を振るシミュレーションをするだけですよね？
I've never been trained to swing
スイングの訓練を受けたことがない
then play that one
それからそれをプレイしてください
Every time halfway through the game, the plane is like this
ゲームの途中で毎回飛行機はこうなります
just come down
ただ降りてください
But no matter how much I fall, it won't affect me
でもどれだけ落ちても私には影響しないよ
right or wrong
正しいか間違っているか
because it is safe to experiment with
安全に実験できるからです
This is a very good market pattern
これは非常に良い市場パターンです
There is indeed such a function on the Internet
インターネットには確かにそのような機能があります
I do have a lot we can't do in practice
練習ではできないことがたくさんある
For example, if you do a chemistry experiment
たとえば、化学の実験をすると、
Can you fail safely in a lab?
実験室で安全に失敗できるでしょうか?
maybe come back once
一度戻ってくるかもしれない
But the network can continue to repeat
しかし、ネットワークは繰り返しを続けることができます
you find the best
あなたは最高のものを見つけます
And the second network also has a
2 番目のネットワークにも、
One advantage of online teaching materials
オンライン教材のメリットの一つ
able to control
コントロールできる
You can control the progress of teaching
授業の進行状況をコントロールできる
Can control parameter changes
パラメータの変更を制御できる
You can go to a parameter for a Spring-style change
Spring スタイルの変更のパラメータに移動できます
and watch it change
そしてそれが変化するのを見てください
I can do it all
全部できるよ
There is also a section on humanities
人文科学分野もあります
The humanities part is not easy to present on the Internet
人文科学の部分はインターネット上で発表するのが難しい
this is the truth
これが真実だ
Natural science is better presented
自然科学はより良く表現されている
But the humanities part should present really good teaching content through the Internet
しかし、人文科学の部分はインターネットを通じて本当に優れた教育コンテンツを提供する必要があります
sometimes bad presentation
時々ひどいプレゼンテーション
Sometimes a face-to-face learning between people is better
場合によっては、人々の間で対面で学習する方が良い場合もあります
So the factor that emphasizes the so-called powder layer practice is here
したがって、ここではいわゆるパウダーレイヤーの実践が強調されています。
That is to say, there are some things that you can learn through the Internet
つまり、インターネットを通じて学べることもあります。
If there are some units, you study in the classroom
いくつかの単元がある場合は教室で勉強します
or study in the lab
または研究室で勉強する
so this place is one of its focal points
この場所はその中心の一つです
Another tutorial that is increasingly emphasizing social groups and motivation
社会的グループとモチベーションをますます強調する別のチュートリアル
because of online learning
オンライン学習のおかげで
Cooperative Learning
協同学習
But the place where you study is you alone
でも君が勉強する場所は君だけだ
Well, there is also the aftermath of this on the Internet.
さて、ネット上ではこの余波もあります。
This is all to be dealt with
これはすべて対処すべきことです
In addition, learning tools will become more and more simple
さらに、学習ツールはますますシンプルになります
will become easier
楽になります
Especially after silverization
特に銀化後は
Silverized complex placed on the silver side
銀面に配置された銀化複合体
right
右
Simple as a tablet for your personal use
個人用途向けのタブレットとしてシンプル
So the computer is no longer as complicated as a normal personal computer
したがって、コンピュータはもはや通常のパーソナルコンピュータほど複雑ではありません
It's about how to make a connection between these places
これらの場所をどのように接続するかについてです
Therefore, there are a lot of things that need to be gradually stored in the reprinted computer.
したがって、再版コンピュータに徐々に保存しなければならないことがたくさんあります。
Especially Taiwan's IC chip design is very powerful
特に台湾のICチップ設計は非常に強力です
As long as you can imagine it is designed for you
あなたが想像できる限り、それはあなたのためにデザインされています
So the tool itself can be hardened
ツール自体を強化できるため、
Learning tools can be hardened in the future
学習ツールは将来的に強化される可能性がある
In addition, there are formal learning
さらに、正式な学習もあります
There are more and more opportunities for Informal learning
非公式な学習の機会がますます増えています
The need for education is increasing
教育の必要性が高まっている
So if you have a look at Luohu Tools
Luohu Tools をご覧ください。
You can often see many students sitting in a certain portrait
ある肖像画の中に多くの学生が座っているのをよく見かけます
then draw
それから描きます
So they've been trained like this since they were little
だから彼らは小さい頃からそうやって訓練されてきたんだ
This is all formal learning
これはすべて正式な学習です
In addition, the simulation type and the game type
また、シミュレーションタイプとゲームタイプ
You can also do humanities subjects like simulation
シミュレーションなどの文系科目も受講可能
Humanities can also be simulated
文系も模擬できる
Not that only physical chemistry
物理化学だけではありません
because you can simulate situations
状況をシミュレーションできるから
Can do situational simulation
状況に応じたシミュレーションができる
There is a way of learning called
という学習方法があります。
the kind called
と呼ばれる種類
writing with situational awareness
状況認識を持って書く
what does it mean
どういう意味ですか
Let's say we're driving
車を運転しているとしましょう
We must drive to the coach field
私たちはコーチ場まで車で行かなければなりません
After the coaching field exam
コーチ実技試験終了後
you have a driver's license
あなたは運転免許証を持っています
but where is the problem
しかし、どこに問題があるのでしょうか
Does having a driver's license mean you can drive?
運転免許証を持っているということは、運転できるということですか？
not necessarily
必ずしも
because you didn't practice the situation
その状況を実践していないからです
you go uphill
あなたは上り坂を行きます
then start uphill
それから上り坂を開始します
And the condition of various roads
そして、さまざまな道路の状況
you haven't practiced
あなたは練習していない
this is
これは
Cut and sweep the cognitive writing of that situation
その状況の認識を切り取ってスキャンする
there is another one like this
こんなのもう一つあります
I remember
私は覚えています
I remember exercising
運動したのを覚えています
then golf
それからゴルフ
I don't know how to fight
戦い方が分からない
So I go to the driving range every time
だから私は毎回ゴルフ練習場に行きます
When it comes to the driving range
ドライビングレンジといえば
I actually played well
実際よく遊んでたし
Easy to play every time
いつでも簡単にプレイできる
Then I went to Australia once
それから一度オーストラリアに行きました
Then my friend said let's continue to play the scene
それから私の友人は、そのシーンを続けて再生しましょうと言いました
it's my first time
初めてです
It's really embarrassing the first time
初めてだと本当に恥ずかしいです
Why
なぜ
'Cause I can't even hit the first ball
初球すら打てないから
a lot of people lined up behind
後ろにたくさんの人が並んでいた
What's Next to Receive Situational Awareness
状況認識を得るために次に何をすべきか
That is to say, you did not go to that situation to write
つまり、あなたは書くためにその状況に行ったわけではありません。
So you don't even know what date you want to work at this time
つまり、現時点では何日に働きたいのかさえわかりません
you don't even know
あなたも知らない
So this is also a
したがって、これも
Sometimes it can be shaped like this in a simulated environment
シミュレートされた環境ではこのように形成される場合があります
let you experience
体験させてください
Opportunities to write interest other than knowledge
知識以外の興味を書く機会
I think this has just been said
これは今言われたばかりだと思います
This category is a case like this
このカテゴリはこんなケースです
I'm probably talking about this very briefly
おそらくこれについて非常に簡単に話していると思います
Then there's a little time for you guys to ask questions.
その後、皆さんに少し質問する時間があります。
we make an interaction
私たちは相互作用をします
make an interaction
インタラクションをする
Do you have
ありますか
All questions please
すべての質問をお願いします
It is very simple to ask Principal Zhang three questions
張校長に 3 つの質問をするのはとても簡単です。
The first question is the APP software of your rigid body
最初の質問は、剛体 APP ソフトウェアです。
That is to say, in the future, the camp software will pass through this.
つまり、将来的にはキャンプのソフトウェアがこれを通過することになります。
please explain his
彼のことを説明してください
his usefulness
彼の有用性
but the second is you
でも2番目はあなたです
Did Principal Zhang think that the Three Kingdoms game
張校長は三国志ゲームだと思ったのか？
computer games for kids
子供向けのコンピューターゲーム
Parents can rest assured
親も安心できる
the third is
3つ目は
In addition to storage
保管に加えて
Ask Principal Zhang if he has other functions
張校長に他の任務があるかどうか尋ねる
Thanks
ありがとう
I think the future development of the camp is really a lot
キャンプの今後の展開は本当に色々だと思います
because he has a lot of small supplies
彼は小さな物資をたくさん持っているから
For example, his sister has a problem in your life
たとえば、彼の妹があなたの人生に問題を抱えているとします。
And he sells them very cheaply
そして彼はそれらを非常に安く販売します
say 0.99
0.99と言います
$0.99 and more
0.99ドル以上
then look now
それなら今見てください
There are many functions now
今は色々な機能がありますが
I don't know what function it has for commuting.
通勤用としてはどのような機能があるのか​​は分かりません。
no no no
ダメダメダメ
There are a lot of software in his APP Store
彼のAPP Storeにはたくさんのソフトウェアがあります
Then in your APP Store
次に、APP Storeで
There are various application agents
さまざまな申請エージェントがあります
So as long as you want all kinds of application agents
したがって、あらゆる種類のアプリケーションエージェントが必要な限り、
It can be converted into an APP in the camp
キャンプ内でAPP化可能
So he has a great range
だから彼は守備範囲が広いんだよ
So in fact our generation
つまり実際に私たちの世代は
must face that problem
その問題に直面しなければならない
Everyone must go to understand the camp
全員がキャンプを理解するために行かなければなりません
Sometimes we ask ourselves children are faster
私たちは時々、子どものほうが速いのではないかと自問します。
Because kids are great
子供ってすごいから
Because they have a high chance of cooperative learning
協調学習の可能性が高いため
They can exchange experiences with each other
お互いに経験を交換できる
So sometimes ask him
それで時々彼に尋ねます
what kind of software do you want
どのようなソフトウェアが欲しいですか
If you ask him, he can find it for you.
彼に尋ねれば、彼はあなたのためにそれを見つけてくれるでしょう。
You can also read newspapers, magazines
新聞や雑誌も読めます
now have
現在都有
How are we now, Master Shi?
師先生、私たちは今どうですか？
is lent the tablet to the students
タブレットは生徒に貸し出されています
We're here to borrow a book, not a book
私たちは本を借りに来たのではなく、本を借りに来たのです
is a tablet for you
あなたのためのタブレットです
Then there are a lot of e-books in this tablet
このタブレットには電子書籍がたくさん入っています
We also caused him to lend him
私たちも彼に貸してもらいました
You pay it back in about two weeks
2週間程度で返金してもらえます
So the qualitative change of the library will also change in the future
図書館の質的変化も今後変わっていくだろう
He's not borrowing a book, he's borrowing a vehicle
彼は本を借りているのではなく、車を借りているのです
In fact, I read e-books like this
実際に私はこんな電子書籍を読んでいます
So this will have many functions in the future
将来的にはこれに多くの機能が追加される予定です
Not only educational function
教育機能だけではない
I am not only educational
私は教育的なだけではありません
As for gamification software
ゲーミフィケーションソフトに関しては
really pick carefully
本当に慎重に選んでください
In fact, I can only see now
実は今しか見えない
a long time ago
ずっと前に
because he cosplays
彼はコスプレをするので
A lot of fun
とても楽しいこと
but he's cosplaying
でも彼はコスプレをしている
Is there a transfer learning effect?
転移学習効果はあるのでしょうか？
I don't think he has the knowledge to pass on
彼には伝えられるほどの知識がないと思う
but he has
しかし彼は持っています
The main thing I gave that example is
例としてあげた主なものは、
He has changed your values
彼はあなたの価値観を変えました
this is one of his
これは彼のものです
This value change is sometimes impossible in transactions.
この値の変更はトランザクションでは不可能な場合があります。
So it is also very difficult
だからそれもすごく難しいんです
but i don't encourage
でも私は奨励しません
The kind that really let children play too much game
本当に子供たちにゲームをさせすぎたタイプ
that software
そのソフトウェア
Because our current game software is very violent
現在のゲームソフトは非常に暴力的であるため、
Yes, so I asked Principal Zhang for advice.
はい、それで張校長にアドバイスを求めました。
Is that the Romance of the Three Kingdoms game for children to give up?
それは子供が諦める三国志ゲームでしょうか？
Now that was ten years ago
それはもう10年前のことです
probably gone now
おそらくもう行ってしまった
it's gone now
もうなくなってしまった
so you still have to see
だからまだ見なければなりません
what's the best now
今何が最高ですか
best now
今が一番いい
at least i personally think
少なくとも私は個人的に思う
I don't see anything I like so far
今のところ気に入ったものはありません
Even though it's billed as educational software
教育用ソフトウェアとして請求されているにもかかわらず
But I think its educational model is wrong
しかし、その教育モデルは間違っていると思います
For example, there is a software that writes English
たとえば、英語を書くソフトウェアがあります。
English teaching
英文教學
That English is called designing a screen
その英語は画面をデザインするという
I design a picture
画面デザインをします
After designing a screen
画面デザインが終わったら
There are many screens such as
などの画面がたくさんあります。
Just make a seawater anomaly
海水異常を起こすだけ
Then the children can
そうすれば、子供たちはできる
seawater anomaly project
海水異常プロジェクト
you can click it and it will be given to you
それをクリックすればあなたに与えられます
Then click on each word to practice calligraphy for you
次に、各単語をクリックしてカリグラフィーを練習します。
But the problem is that kids won't order that.
しかし問題は、子供たちがそれを注文しないことです。
He can point to seawater anomalies such as parasols
彼はパラソルなどの海水の異常を指摘できる
He ordered a parasol parasol and it became a what
彼は日傘を注文しました、そしてそれは何になりました
turn into a rocket and swing out
ロケットになって振り出す
do you know what i mean
分かりますか
At that point, the animation of a certain object will come out.
そのとき、あるオブジェクトのアニメーションが出てきます。
I think this
私はこう思います
It was selling well
よく売れてた
But in terms of our education, that is useless
でも私たちの教育という観点からはそれは役に立たない
why is it useless
なぜ駄目なのか
Because the students don't know how to click the English skill
生徒たちは英語スキルのクリック方法を知らないため
he's already going to something
彼はすでに何かに向かっています
click on those objects
それらのオブジェクトをクリックします
Watch the animation behind them
背後にあるアニメーションをご覧ください
so i said i think about it later
だから後で考えるって言った
Barely say he is useful, say he is more humorous
彼は役に立つとはほとんど言わず、彼はもっとユーモラスだと言う
Because the production of his objects is beyond our imagination
なぜなら、彼の作品の制作は私たちの想像を超えているからです。
You said learning English is really useless
英語の勉強は本当に役に立たないって言ってたね
So sometimes from an educational point of view
ですから、時には教育的な観点から
educational software
教育用ソフトウェア
won't be very useful
あまり役に立たないでしょう
There are a lot of educational software that I think is wrong
間違っていると思う教育ソフトウェアがたくさんあります
is not right
正しくない
Also his animation is wrong
彼のアニメーションも間違っています
For example, many of his gamified educational software
たとえば、彼のゲーム化された教育ソフトウェアの多くは、
an apple falls
リンゴが落ちる
two apples fell
リンゴが２個落ちた
ask you how many apples
リンゴは何個あるか尋ねてください
make me plan is game
私に計画を立てるのはゲームです
The first one is less fun
最初のものはあまり面白くありません
That's a multimedia quiz, you know what I mean?
それはマルチメディアに関するクイズです、私が言いたいことはわかりますか？
so be careful
ので注意してください
So why is there such research on the market saying
では、なぜ市場で次のような研究が行われているのでしょうか。
We want to import formal
正規品を輸入したい
Instead of letting manufacturers use it directly
メーカーに直接使用させるのではなく
Designing this software from the perspective of no cognitive theory
認知理論のない観点からこのソフトウェアを設計する
The most important thing is such a situation
一番大事なのはこういう状況だ
So that needs to be tuned and done carefully
したがって、調整して慎重に行う必要があります
not quite right
まったく正しくありません
In fact, this assistance community should be able to do it.
実際、この支援コミュニティはそれができるはずです。
but if do
しかし、もしそうなら
Make a comment on each game software
各ゲームソフトについてコメントする
we may be thrown eggs
私たちは卵を投げ込まれるかもしれない
It's more troublesome at this point
この時点でもっと面倒だ
ok thank you professor thank you
わかりました、ありがとう、教授、ありがとう
ok guys no more questions
はい、もう質問はありません
come please
来てください
please teach me
教えて下さい
There are more and more opportunities for modern people to use computers
現代人がパソコンを使う機会はますます増えています
Fewer and fewer opportunities for assistance
援助の機会はますます少なくなっています
An old human like me will
私のような年老いた人間はそうするだろう
often forget what help
助けを忘れることが多い
that overemphasizes computer teaching
コンピューター教育を過度に強調する
What about new humans?
新人類はどうなるの？
So we just said that we must know each other
だから私たちはお互いを知らなければならないと言いました
very important
とても重要な
Some still need physical teaching
まだ体育の指導が必要な人もいる
so don't
だからやめてください
To think that the computer can expect us
コンピューターが私たちを期待できると考えるとは
Because in many theories
なぜなら、多くの理論では
This part of Practice still needs to
練習のこの部分はまだ必要です
actually do it
実際にやってみよう
this is impossible
不可能だよ
so i just said
だから私はちょうど言った
computers are really fascinating
コンピューターは本当に面白いです
but it is easy to cause silverstone
ただしシルバーストーンが発生しやすい
so why are we pushing this
ではなぜこれを推進するのか
When computerized bloodshed
コンピューター化された流血事件が起きたとき
Also pay attention to its sequelae
後遺症にも注意
Then also pay attention to when it uses
次に、使用するタイミングにも注意してください
If you can't grasp this point
この点が理解できないと
yes it will affect
はい、影響します
But we can't both
でも私たち両方はできない
you know what i mean ? because this is a period
意味が分かりますか？これは期間だからです
because it will
そうなるから
You don't want to be affected and you will be affected
影響を受けたくないのに、影響を受けることになる
This is like talking about networking
これはネットワークについて話しているようなものです
Many textbooks are wrong
多くの教科書は間違っています
I remember a teacher once said
かつて先生が言っていたのを覚えています
Then this is called wrong, we all should not read this kind of textbook
それならこれは間違っていると言われます、私たちは皆この種の教科書を読むべきではありません
but you must have
しかし、あなたは持っている必要があります
but with a different attitude
しかし、違う態度で
Then you go to the wrong place to find
それからあなたは間違った場所に行って見つけます
find something wrong
何か間違っていることを見つける
So just use the one that
したがって、次のものを使用してください
when and how to use
いつ、どのように使用するか
is important
は重要
then this is us
それならこれが私たちです
unless we don't
そうしない限り
Don't computerize everything
すべてを電子化しないでください
But as long as computerized
しかし、コンピュータ化されている限り、
This is a phenomenon that must be faced
これは直視しなければならない現象です
This is
これは
it brings convenience
それは利便性をもたらします
But it also has repercussions
しかし、それは影響も及ぼします
There are some words we often forget too
私たちも忘れがちな言葉があります
right
右
because of the enemy
敵のせいで
Now the enemy has this problem
今、敵はこの問題を抱えています
So your concern is the existence of
つまり、あなたの懸念は、
But what we really want to care about
でも私たちが本当に大切にしたいのは
find a way to make it normal
それを正常にする方法を見つける
Do you have any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
please
お願いします
Like Professor Zhang's answer just now
今の張教授の答えのように
i thought of a question
質問を考えました
In fact, what students need most is
実際、学生が最も必要としているのは、
he has the ability to judge
彼は判断する能力がある
what is good quality
品質が良いとは何ですか
That
それか
that is
あれは
Now
現在
you can know say
あなたは言うことができます
A lot of game software is not that good
あまり良くないゲームソフトが多い
But
しかし
Like all parents, the primary concern is
すべての親と同様に、一番の関心事は次のとおりです。
Do you still have the ability to judge
まだ判断力あるのか
right
右
This leads to the essence of education
それが教育の本質につながる
In fact, we in Taiwan are really admitted
実際、私たち台湾人は本当に認められています
Dreaming that there are many abnormal teaching
異常な指導が多い夢
it's really helpless
本当に無力だ
Because this is no longer a question of so-called educational ideals
これはもはやいわゆる教育理念の問題ではないからです。
but a political issue
しかし政治的な問題
As long as there are political issues, many things are unsolvable
政治問題がある限り解決できないことは多い
But it's also a question of fairness
しかしそれは公平性の問題でもある
Because we haven't developed
うちは発展してないから
Come out on that what communication skills
コミュニケーション能力は何なのか出てきてください
Its venom ability a good Pacific system
優れた太平洋システムの毒能力
Then as long as your school is divided into good schools and bad schools
そうすると、学校が良い学校と悪い学校に分かれる限り、
there is this problem
この問題があります
so this is
それでこれは
So we are not a normal teaching
ですから私たちは普通の教えではありません
I want to promote in Normal University recently
最近師範大学に進学したいと思っています
Put that maliciousness and the three evils into effect
その悪意と三悪を実行せよ
You students, don't talk nonsense
学生諸君、くだらないことを言うな
I'm just pushing right now
ただ今推してます
Why?
なぜ？
because I always feel
いつも感じているから
It is not easy for you to get into a school
学校に入学するのは簡単ではありません
then why don't you give it
それならなぜあげないのですか
give it a little more time to study
もう少し勉強する時間を与えてください
give it some chance
チャンスを与えてください
Especially our boys are relatively slow in academic achievement
特に我が家の息子たちは学力の伸びが比較的遅いです。
to show
見せる
then you should let
それならさせるべきです
It's not about his character
彼は性格の問題ではない
right
右
But we talk to many actors like me
しかし、私たちは私のような多くの俳優と話します
You said I said people want to play tricks
あなたは言いました、私は人はいたずらをしたいと言いました
like us say we shadow play
私たちが言うように、私たちは影絵遊びをします
Can't go home every time
毎回家に帰れない
because he thinks he
彼はそう思うから
He scored very well in the entrance examination
彼は入学試験でとても良い成績をとった
I'm only ten points away.
あと10点しか離れていない。
right
右
Then what does it matter if you make him look like this?
では、彼をこのように見せて何が問題になるのでしょうか？
and you're not
そしてあなたはそうではありません
unless your resources are limited
リソースが限られている場合を除き、
Because there are so many in one class
一つのクラスにたくさんの人がいるから
If you transfer in, he may not be able to attend class.
転入すると授業に出席できなくなる可能性があります。
Otherwise, do you try to let him turn?
そうでなければ、彼を振り向かせようとしますか？
because we have a survey
アンケートがあるので
that's really scary
それは本当に怖いです
We have a program from our Normal University called
私たちの師範大学には、と呼ばれるプログラムがあります。
Higher Education Database
高等教育資料庫
So we will analyze the situation of each school
そこで各学校の状況を分析していきます
Then put the students
それから生徒たちを入れて、
why do you write this department
なぜこの部門を書くのですか
Why did you study this school
なぜこの学校に通ったのか
More than half are based on the opinions of parents and teachers
半数以上は親や教師の意見による
really so
本当にそうです
and then after coming in
そして入ってから
related to his information after coming in
入国後の彼の情報に関連する
In fact, a certain percentage is irrelevant
実際には、一定の割合は関係ありません
He didn't want to read it
彼はそれを読みたくなかった
but he came in
しかし彼は入ってきた
why don't you let him at the college level
なぜ彼を大学レベルに行かせてくれないのか
Go after what he wants to do
彼のやりたいことを追いかける
what's the matter with spending a little more time
もう少し時間をかけても何が問題ですか
For example, it should be a normal four-year graduation
たとえば、通常の4年制卒業であるべきです。
what does it matter if it takes two more years
あと2年かかったらどうなるの？
There are many who are not graduating
卒業しない人もたくさんいる
Achievements higher than ours abound
私たちを超える実績はたくさんあります
right
右
So sometimes the idea is to change
だから時にはアイデアを変えることもある
But this place needs time to adjust
しかし、この場所は調整する時間が必要です
For example, I always feel
例えば、私がいつも感じるのは、
Twelve Zero Country is a very important part
十二のゼロカントリーは非常に重要な部分です
That is to say, if he can
つまり、もしできるなら、
Take this Metal Ability well
このメタルアビリティを上手に活用しましょう
come out with good faith
誠意を持って出てくる
In fact, our competitiveness in the future is very strong
実際、私たちの将来の競争力は非常に強いです
Look at how much we learn how to communicate.
私たちがどれだけコミュニケーション方法を学んでいるかを見てください。
Powerpoint won't do either
パワーポイントでもダメ
Knowledge collation will not write that report
ナレッジ照合ではそのレポートは作成されません
it's bad too, isn't it?
それも悪いですよね？
It's all about faith
すべては信仰の問題です
have faith
都要信念的
so this is your question
これがあなたの質問です
is a big environmental problem
大きな環境問題です
We can't even do our own mistakes
私たちは自分自身の間違いさえ犯すことができません
How to judge whether this thing is good or bad
これが良いか悪いかをどう判断するか
right
右
In fact, the whole paragraph can't come out.
実際、段落全体は出てきません。
how do you judge
どう判断しますか
Because we can't blame the kids
子どもたちを責めることはできないから
we didn't give him a chance
私たちは彼にチャンスを与えなかった
In addition, I think the next generation
また、次世代だと思います
like i have many assistants
アシスタントがたくさんいるように
We often say that our symbiosis is a strawberry family
私たちの共生はイチゴの家族だとよく言います
I don't even admit it
認めてもいない
Then his hard work
それから彼の努力は
Then
それから
Then job status
次にジョブステータス
sometimes surpass us
時々私たちを超える
Never heard of them buying business
彼らがビジネスを買収したという話は聞いたことがない
So don't say that we kids are strawberries
だから、私たち子供がイチゴだなんて言わないでください
I have found many assistants
たくさんのアシスタントを見つけました
I feel after passing
過ぎてから感じること
Our next generation is actually very promising
私たちの次世代は実際に非常に有望です
It's just that we have to give him a good direction
ただ、私たちは彼に良い方向性を与えなければなりません
good direction to do
やるべき良い方向性
OK
OK
Excuse me
すみません
take the opportunity
機会を利用します
flower old man
花の老人
OK, do you have any other questions?
OK、他に質問はありますか？
please
お願いします
Vice-Chancellor
副校長
Excuse me
すみません
i have a test question
テストの問題があります
Will the quiz questions be asked publicly again?
クイズの問題は再び公開されるのでしょうか?
no
いいえ
I said it's about me personally
私個人のことだと言いました
more benefits
さらなるメリット
I am the one who ate for 38 years
38年間食べ続けてきたのは私です
So I had an earlier review of the store
ということで、以前お店のレビューをさせていただきました
so I
だから私は
I'm disgusted, I don't want to study
嫌だ、勉強したくない
Because our time was
なぜなら私たちの時代は
Erection skill
勃血強技
From middle school to high school and then Wuzhuan University
中学から高校、そして五宣大学へ
grind out
粉砕する
Then I always feel that the children now
それから私はいつも感じます、今の子供たちは
From the very beginning, I objected to my children learning that computer
私は最初から子供たちがそのコンピューターを学ぶことに反対していました
He becomes knowledge easy to get
得やすい知識になる
easy to forget
忘れやすい
If you ask him, he knows everything
彼に尋ねれば、彼はすべてを知っています
I don't learn it myself but
自分では習っていないのですが、
wow recently i played that
わあ、最近それをプレイしました
After that smartphone, wow, that sucks
あのスマホの後、うわー、ひどいよ
This computer is really fascinating
このコンピュータは本当に魅力的です
But now the power is not good
でも今は勢いが良くない
I can't write it from scratch
一から書けない
that's why i want to say
だからこそ私は言いたいのです
directly from this tablet
このタブレットから直接
Will there be a camp after the intervention?
介入後にキャンプは行われるのでしょうか？
we don't need
私たちには必要ありません
You don't have to work so hard to create a
作成するのにそれほど苦労する必要はありません
your database
あなたのデータベース
So is this okay?
それで、これは大丈夫ですか？
I think from a learning point of view this is
学習の観点からするとこれだと思います
Good practice, because there will be no standard in the future
将来的には標準が存在しないため、適切な実践を行ってください。
software
ソフトウェア
There's no standard software either, anyway.
いずれにしても、標準のソフトウェアはありません。
and now the interface is very simple
インターフェースは非常にシンプルになりました
Yeah
うん
But get used to the environment
でも環境に慣れる
After you get used to the environment and establish
環境に慣れて定着したら
For example, you are used to communicating with others on the Internet.
たとえば、あなたはインターネット上で他の人とコミュニケーションをとることに慣れています。
Because some of them I haven’t faced face to face, why should I communicate with you?
直接会ったことのない人もいるのに、なぜコミュニケーションを取る必要があるのでしょうか?
it's a matter of habit
それは習慣の問題です
adaptation problem
適応の問題
I think after you get used to it
慣れてからだと思います
In fact, this can be learned at any time
実はこれはいつでも学べるのです
I began to think that there might be many bad things about computers
コンピュータには悪いことがたくさんあるかもしれないと思い始めた
recently feel
最近感じる
I wear it together in the morning
朝一緒に着ています
See which PPC can choose that
どの PPC がそれを選択できるかを確認してください
important topic
重要な話題
This solves it
これで解決です
No wonder there is something wrong with the body
あの男に何か問題があるのも不思議ではない
Immediately fell for Google to find
すぐにGoogleに見つかってしまいました
wow still very convenient
うわー、まだとても便利です
Much faster than finding a doctor
医者を探すよりずっと早い
and believe
そして信じます
do you believe it
あなたはそれを信じていますか
I have a lot of questions about the Normal University in
師範大学についてたくさん質問があります
know on the internet
インターネットで知る
So I know what's wrong with many of our students
だから私は多くの生徒の何が問題なのかを知っています
Because it is easy for me to find the information inside
中の情報が見つけやすいので
Now what I want to write is that the first private school is not good
さて書きたいのは、最初の私立はダメだということです
then many
それからたくさんの
you that you use again
また使うあなた
The tablet will zoom in and out
タブレットはズームインおよびズームアウトします
Yes, that's what I said, just intervene directly from this
はい、私が言ったことです、ここから直接介入してください
don't intervene
介入しないでください
ok ok ok
わかりました、わかりました
Because in fact, our previous education was more of a crow style.
なぜなら、実際のところ、私たちの以前の教育はカラス式だったからです。
For example, you might be interested in literature
たとえば、あなたは文学に興味があるかもしれません
So your literature will remember
そうすればあなたの文学は記憶に残るでしょう
But I can ask you how much physical chemistry do you remember?
しかし、物理化学をどのくらい覚えているか尋ねてもいいですか?
So sometimes the cultivation of learning ability is still very important.
したがって、時には学習能力を養うことが依然として非常に重要です。
Then you will naturally memorize the part you are interested in
そうすれば、興味のある部分は自然と覚えられます
now we are not
今はそうではありません
Now we all have to write
今、私たち全員が書かなければなりません
After finishing high school, this is a common problem
高校卒業後、これはよくある問題です
Like my personal history and geography is okay
私の個人的な経歴や地理は大丈夫です
forget that chemistry
その化学を忘れてください
none of them are there
誰もそこにいない
yes
はい
Thanks
ありがとう
Are there any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
please
お願いします
I would like to ask about the positioning of future teachers
将来の教員の位置付けについてお聞きします。
Because recently, for example, I was looking at the formula
たとえば最近、私は次の式を見ていたからです。
The justice of the micro-sender
マイクロ送信者の正義
Harvard OpenCourseWare
ハーバードオープンコースウェア
We also know that MIT actually had these things a few years ago
MIT が数年前に実際にこれらのことを行っていたこともわかっています。
In China, it is like Mr. Lu, a medicine man from the East China Sea
中国で言うと東シナ海の祈祷師ルーさんのようなものです
A lot of the process of class is PO up
授業のプロセスの多くはPOアップです
And as long as the students of that relevant course go up to watch
そして、その関連コースの学生が見に行く限り、
Maybe the teachers in their school have been compared
もしかしたら自分の学校の先生も比べられたのかもしれない
If future teachers develop like this technology
将来の教師がこのようなテクノロジーを開発したら
A lot of distance learning has turned into saying that you can actually learn more than online
多くの遠隔学習は、実際にはオンラインよりも多くのことを学べると主張するようになりました
Better than school, the positioning of future teachers
学校よりも優れた、将来の教師の位置付け
In which direction should it develop
どの方向に発展するべきか
I mentioned that just now, actually
先ほども言いましたが、実は
Transfer of knowledge through the Internet
インターネットを介した知識の伝達
If you are really like the teacher you said
あなたが本当に先生の言う通りなら
He is very proud of all aspects
彼はあらゆる面でとても誇りに思っています
Then maybe you can watch it at home
それなら家でも見れるかも
then no problem
それなら問題ない
That's not the problem now
今はそれが問題ではない
Questions have many non-knowledgeable parts
質問には知識のない部分が多くあります
The human learning of the non-knowledge part is different
人間の非知識部分の学習は異なります
It is very difficult to express through textbooks
教科書で表現するのはとても難しい
That's why I said that teachers in the future have to transform
だからこそ私は、これからの教師は変革しなければならないと言いました。
I said that after my student opened an underground website
私の生徒がアンダーグラウンドのウェブサイトを開いた後、私はそう言いました
I'm starting to transform
私は変身し始めています
Because I know I can't teach my students anymore
もう生徒に教えることはできないと分かっているから
in computer skills section
コンピュータースキルセクションで
Section in Computer Science
コンピュータサイエンスセクション
What I want to teach is inquiry ability
教えたいのは探究力
how to teach them how to form questions
質問の作り方をどのように教えるか
how to solve the problem
問題を解決する方法
How to use his creativity
彼の創造性をどう活かすか
will be different
違うだろう
So don't be afraid that humans will disappear
だから人類が消滅することを恐れないでください
human beings must have value
人間には価値がなければならない
My computer only expects a small part of us
私のコンピューターは私たちのほんの一部だけを期待しています
a small part
小さな部分
So we're still valuable
だから私たちはまだ価値がある
so don't worry too much about this
だからこれについてはあまり心配しないでください
It's not the disappearance of humans, it's the disappearance of teachers
人間が消えたんじゃなくて、先生が消えたんだ
no
いいえ
Not a Teacher Transformation
教師の変革ではない
The teacher is going to transfer
先生が転勤することになりました
Even your teacher should start to know slowly
先生も徐々に分かってくるはずです
Knowledge conveys such a
知識はそのようなことを伝えます
A role will slowly decrease
徐々に役割が減っていく
then you may have to change your other character
その場合は他のキャラクターを変更する必要があるかもしれません
So why are there so many institutes now
ではなぜこれほど多くの研究機関があるのでしょうか？
It doesn't matter if he doesn't go to class at all.
彼が授業にまったく行かなくても問題ありません。
I don't care even if you have fewer co-marriages
同伴婚が少なくても気にしない
no required courses
必須のコースはありません
You're going to read this book because you're doing research.
あなたは研究をしているのでこの本を読むつもりです。
right
右
Why must the teacher teach you
なぜ先生はあなたに教えなければならないのですか
Then the teacher will act differently
そうすれば先生の態度も変わります
different so there will be an adjustment
同じではないので調整が入ります
There will be an adjustment, you are a primary school student
調整があります、あなたは小学生です
Primary school students are definitely not just passing on knowledge
小学生は決して知識を伝えるだけではありません
Universities are more knowledge transfer
大学はより多くの知識を伝達します
The development of training habits in all aspects of elementary school
小学校のあらゆる面でトレーニング習慣を身につける
In the past, we put too much emphasis on knowledge
これまで私たちは知識を重視しすぎていました
while ignoring other aspects
他の側面を無視しながら
After that, other aspects may arise
その後、別の側面が現れる可能性があります
Then this teacher is going to change
そしたらこの先生も変わるよ
My teacher is going to change
先生が変わるよ
Do you have any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
Very close
とても近い
we are usually two
私たちはいつも二人です
Anyone else want to ask, kid, do you want to ask?
他に聞きたい人はいますか？
this can't stop
これは止まらない
Then we listened to this speech by Principal Zhang
その後、張校長の講演を聞きました。
For this infinite world of digital learning
この無限のデジタル学習の世界のために
have an understanding
有一個了解
I'm with him to host this digital point chief
私は彼と一緒にこのデジタルポイントチーフを主催します
Meeting with Digital Learning National Project
デジタル学習国家プロジェクトとの打ち合わせ
For the first time after so many times, I have settled on his comprehensive view.
何度も、私は初めて彼の包括的な見解に落ち着きました。
I am Principal Zhang
私は張校長です
The Dean also reminds us
学部長も私たちに思い出させます
There are a lot of side effects
副作用がたくさんある
And that's only a small part of it
そしてそれはほんの一部にすぎません
So there are many places in this
この中にはたくさんの場所がありますので、
still worth exploring
まだ探索する価値があります
his lecturer i think of a book
彼の講師である私は本のことを考えています
author of this book
この本の著者
was a physical chemist in the first half of the second century
は2世紀前半の物理化学者でした
physical chemist
物理化学者
But he later studied physical chemistry
しかし、彼は後に物理化学を学びました
The original chapter is the last
原章都最後
he turned to philosophy
彼は哲学に転向した
and become a famous philosopher
そして有名な哲学者になる
His son won the Nobel Prize with Dean Li
息子はディーン・リーとともにノーベル賞を受賞
his name is prangli
彼の名前はプランリです
He is a Hungarian nobleman
彼はハンガリーの貴族です
He wrote a book called Personal Knowledge
彼は「Personal Knowledge」という本を書きました
personal knowledge
個人知識
this is a classic
これは古典です
I think there may be many people who know
もしかしたらご存知の方も多いかと思いますが、
Personal Knowledge
個人的な知識
This book tells us
この本は私たちに伝えます
There are two kinds of knowledge we learn
私たちが学ぶ知識には2種類あります
One is to concentrate knowledge
一つは知識を集中させること
There is knowledge of resources
資源に関する知識がある
Subsidial Awareness
補助的な意識
is the knowledge of nearby resources
近くのリソースに関する知識です
he may be a hint
彼がヒントになるかもしれない
He may be a person and an atmosphere
人柄や雰囲気かもしれない
he may be a situation
彼は状況かもしれない
he may be a fixer
彼はフィクサーかもしれない
Wait, he may be out of admiration for this authority
待てよ、彼はこの権威に感心していないのかもしれない
And the computer doesn't give you that feeling
そしてコンピューターはその感覚を与えてくれない
He may be because of these things
彼はこれらのことのせいかもしれない
will change your whole study of this
あなたの学習全体が変わります
So the computer may only
したがって、コンピュータは、
Digital learning can be very effective
デジタル学習は非常に効果的です
The knowledge-focused part that helps us complete
完了に役立つ知識中心の部分
resource-conscious part
資源を重視する部分
resource aware part
リソース認識部分
And there is no way to replace the part of the uncle teacher.
そしておじさん教師の役は代えようがありません。
the planney book
プランニーブック
i read it a long time ago
ずっと前に読んだ
In fact, there is something in my impression that he said
実際、私の印象に残っているのは、彼が言ったことです。
In fact, since the 19th century
実は19世紀以降、
Western labs with big breakthroughs
大きな進歩を遂げた欧米の研究機関
Most are in the tradition of his original laboratory
ほとんどは彼の元の研究室の伝統を受け継いでいます
Even if you give him the most complete manual for this tradition
たとえこの伝統に関する最も完全なマニュアルを彼に与えたとしても
He can't learn it all
彼はすべてを学ぶことはできない
he can't help
彼は助けることができない
You give him this instrument
あなたは彼にこの楽器をあげます
You give him all the most complete Manual
あなたは彼に最も完全なマニュアルを渡します
He still can't catch up with you up there.
彼はそこまではまだあなたに追いつけません。
Because he has no Personal Knowledge
彼は個人的な知識を持っていないので、
So I think I totally agree with Principal Zhang on this
したがって、これについては私も張校長に完全に同意すると思います
right here
ここにあります
teacher never dies
先生は決して死なない
teacher only aging
先生だけが老化してる
he will never disappear
彼は決して消えません
Thank you, Principal Zhang
張校長、ありがとうございました